{
  "uniqueId": "JLPT N2",
  "name": "JLPT N2 Reading Quiz",
  "article": "a",
  "instructions": "Type the reading of the below word in Hiragana!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "IMAGE",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "JISHO_QUESTION_WORD",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "NONE",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "QUESTION_AND_ANSWER_LINK_QUESTION",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "answerCompareStrategy": "CONVERT_KANA",
  "compileImages": true,
  "cards": [
    {"meaning":"footprints","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"足跡","answer":["あしあと"]},
    {"meaning":"to keep in custody, to receive on deposit, to take charge of","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"預かる","answer":["あずかる"]},
    {"meaning":"impudent, shameless, brazen","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"厚かましい","answer":["あつかましい"]},
    {"meaning":"to act violently, to rage, to struggle, to be riotous","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"暴れる","answer":["あばれる"]},
    {"meaning":"fat, tallow, lard","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"脂","answer":["あぶら"]},
    {"meaning":"sliding storm door","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"雨戸","answer":["あまど"]},
    {"meaning":"to pamper, to spoil","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"甘やかす","answer":["あまやかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to remain, to be left over, to be in excess, to be too many","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"余る","answer":["あまる"]},
    {"meaning":"knitting, web","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"編物","answer":["あみもの"]},
    {"meaning":"to knit","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"編む","answer":["あむ"]},
    {"meaning":"dangerous, critical, grave","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"危うい","answer":["あやうい"]},
    {"meaning":"rough, rude, wild","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"荒い","answer":["あらい"]},
    {"meaning":"to dispute, to argue, to be at variance, to compete","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"争う","answer":["あらそう"]},
    {"meaning":"another time, again, over again, anew, formally","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改めて","answer":["あらためて"]},
    {"meaning":"to change, to alter, to reform, to revise","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改める","answer":["あらためる"]},
    {"meaning":"to write, to publish","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"著す","answer":["あらわす"]},
    {"meaning":"grateful, thankful, welcome, appreciated, evoking gratitude","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"有難い","answer":["ありがたい"]},
    {"meaning":"to live, to be","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"在る","answer":["ある"]},
    {"meaning":"easy-going","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"安易","answer":["あんい"]},
    {"meaning":"to tell, to tell on (someone), to order","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"言い付ける","answer":["いいつける"]},
    {"meaning":"childcare, nursing, upbringing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"育児","answer":["いくじ"]},
    {"meaning":"on and after, hereafter, thereafter","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"以降","answer":["いこう"]},
    {"meaning":"brave, valiant, gallant, courageous","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"勇ましい","answer":["いさましい"]},
    {"meaning":"necessities of life (food, clothing, etc.)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"衣食住","answer":["いしょくじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"greater, more, further, still more","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一段と","answer":["いちだんと"]},
    {"meaning":"first class, top grade, foremost, top-notch","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一流","answer":["いちりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"fixed, settled, definite","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一定","answer":["いってい"]},
    {"meaning":"moving, transfer, demise","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"移転","answer":["いてん"]},
    {"meaning":"gravity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引力","answer":["いんりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"garden shrubs, trees, potted plant","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"植木","answer":["うえき"]},
    {"meaning":"to float, to rise to surface, to come to mind","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"浮ぶ","answer":["うかぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"to float, to express, to look (sad, glad)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"浮かべる","answer":["うかべる"]},
    {"meaning":"to float, to become merry, to become loose","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"浮く","answer":["うく"]},
    {"meaning":"(hum) to hear, to be told, to know","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"承る","answer":["うけたまわる"]},
    {"meaning":"receipt","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受取","answer":["うけとり"]},
    {"meaning":"to take (be in) charge of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受け持つ","answer":["うけもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"dim, gloomy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"薄暗い","answer":["うすぐらい"]},
    {"meaning":"to dilute, to water down","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"薄める","answer":["うすめる"]},
    {"meaning":"business meeting, previous arrangement, appointment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"打合せ","answer":["うちあわせ"]},
    {"meaning":"to deny, to negate, to contradict","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"打ち消す","answer":["うちけす"]},
    {"meaning":"to bury, to fill up, to fill (a seat, a vacant position)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"埋める","answer":["うめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to show respect, to honour","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"敬う","answer":["うやまう"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn inside out, to turn (something) over","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"裏返す","answer":["うらがえす"]},
    {"meaning":"backdoor, rear entrance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"裏口","answer":["うらぐち"]},
    {"meaning":"to forecast, to predict","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"占う","answer":["うらなう"]},
    {"meaning":"canal, waterway","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"運河","answer":["うんが"]},
    {"meaning":"English-Japanese (e.g. dictionary)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"英和","answer":["えいわ"]},
    {"meaning":"liquid, fluid","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"液体","answer":["えきたい"]},
    {"meaning":"colors, paints","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"絵の具","answer":["えのぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"great, celebrated, eminent, terrible, awful, famous, remarkable, excellent","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"偉い","answer":["えらい"]},
    {"meaning":"horticulture, gardening","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"園芸","answer":["えんげい"]},
    {"meaning":"play (theatrical)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"演劇","answer":["えんげき"]},
    {"meaning":"circumference","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"円周","answer":["えんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"trip, hike, picnic","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遠足","answer":["えんそく"]},
    {"meaning":"extension, elongation, prolongation, lengthening","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"延長","answer":["えんちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"chimney","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"煙突","answer":["えんとつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to chase or run after someone, to run down, to pursue","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"追い掛ける","answer":["おいかける"]},
    {"meaning":"to pass (e.g. car), to outdistance, to outstrip","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"追い越す","answer":["おいこす"]},
    {"meaning":"princess","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"王女","answer":["おうじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"Europe and America, the West","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"欧米","answer":["おうべい"]},
    {"meaning":"to worship, to beg, to make a supplication","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"拝む","answer":["おがむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to compensate for","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"補う","answer":["おぎなう"]},
    {"meaning":"to stop, to restrain, to seize, to repress, to suppress, to press down","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"押える","answer":["おさえる"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to govern, to manage, (2) to subdue","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"治める","answer":["おさめる"]},
    {"question":"痩せる","answer":["やせる"],"meaning":"to become thin; to lose weight; to reduce (one's) weight; to slim, to be barren; to be infertile; to be sterile"},
    {"meaning":"font of purifying water placed at entrance of shrine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"御手洗","answer":["おてあらい"]},
    {"question":"締める","answer":["しめる"],"meaning":"to tie; to fasten; to tighten, to wear (necktie, belt); to put on, to total; to sum, to be strict with, to economize; to economise; to cut down on, to salt; to marinate; to pickle; to make sushi adding a mixture of vinegar and salt"},
    {"question":"廊下","answer":["ろうか"],"meaning":"corridor; hallway; passageway"},
    {"meaning":"lost property","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"落し物","answer":["おとしもの"]},
    {"question":"暇","answer":["ひま","いとま"],"meaning":"spare time; free time; leisure, time (e.g. time it takes to do something), time off; day off; vacation; holiday; leave, quitting (one's job); firing someone; divorcing (one's spouse), (of one's time) free; (of one's business) slow, leaving; departing"},
    {"meaning":"worship, shrine visit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お参り","answer":["おまいり"]},
    {"meaning":"unexpected, casual","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"思い掛けない","answer":["おもいがけない"]},
    {"meaning":"to be under impression that, to be convinced that","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"思い込む","answer":["おもいこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to think of, to hit upon","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"思い付く","answer":["おもいつく"]},
    {"meaning":"thumb","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"親指","answer":["おやゆび"]},
    {"meaning":"greenhouse","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"温室","answer":["おんしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"spa, hot spring, onsen","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"温泉","answer":["おんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"temperate zone","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"温帯","answer":["おんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"and Company, Messrs.","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"御中","answer":["おんちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"shell, shellfish","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"貝","answer":["かい","ばい"]},
    {"meaning":"examination of tickets","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改札","answer":["かいさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"breakup, dissolution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解散","answer":["かいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"sea bathing, seawater bath","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"海水浴","answer":["かいすいよく"]},
    {"meaning":"number of times, frequency","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回数","answer":["かいすう"]},
    {"meaning":"book of tickets","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"回数券","answer":["かいすうけん"]},
    {"meaning":"revision, amendment, alteration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改正","answer":["かいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"good weather","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"快晴","answer":["かいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"explanation, commentary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解説","answer":["かいせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) remodeling, (2) modding (comp)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改造","answer":["かいぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"rotation, revolution, turning","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回転","answer":["かいてん"]},
    {"meaning":"answer, solution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解答","answer":["かいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"reply, answer","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回答","answer":["かいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"the outside, external","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"外部","answer":["がいぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"release, liberation, emancipation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解放","answer":["かいほう"]},
    {"meaning":"open, throw open, liberalization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"開放","answer":["かいほう"]},
    {"meaning":"to warp, to be warped, to curve","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"反る","answer":["かえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to concern oneself in, to have to do with, to affect, to influence, to stick to (opinions)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"係わる","answer":["かかわる"]},
    {"meaning":"writing down, putting on record, recording, making a note of, registration (of mail)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"書留","answer":["かきとめ"]},
    {"meaning":"dictation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"書取","answer":["かきとり"]},
    {"meaning":"individual, each","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"各自","answer":["かくじ"]},
    {"meaning":"science, learning, scholarship","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"学術","answer":["がくじゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"every place, various places","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"各地","answer":["かくち"]},
    {"meaning":"angle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"角度","answer":["かくど"]},
    {"meaning":"department of a university, undergraduate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"学部","answer":["がくぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"exceptional","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"格別","answer":["かくべつ"]},
    {"meaning":"multiplication","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"掛け算","answer":["かけざん"]},
    {"meaning":"downward, descent, fall, drop, subsidence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"下降","answer":["かこう"]},
    {"meaning":"error, blunder, accident","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過失","answer":["かしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"fruit, nut, berry.","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"果実","answer":["かじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"passage, place, point, part","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"個所","answer":["かしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"taxation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"課税","answer":["かぜい"]},
    {"meaning":"underline, underscore","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"下線","answer":["かせん"]},
    {"meaning":"acceleration","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加速","answer":["かそく"]},
    {"meaning":"acceleration","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加速度","answer":["かそくど"]},
    {"meaning":"to put in order, to dispose of, to solve","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"片付く","answer":["かたづく"]},
    {"meaning":"to harden, to solidify, to become firm, to become certain","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"固まる","answer":["かたまる"]},
    {"meaning":"one-way (trip)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"片道","answer":["かたみち"]},
    {"question":"飾る","answer":["かざる"],"meaning":"to decorate; to ornament; to adorn"},
    {"meaning":"to be one-sided, to incline, to be partial","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"片寄る","answer":["かたよる"]},
    {"meaning":"study subject, course of study","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"学科","answer":["がっか"]},
    {"meaning":"to shoulder, to carry on shoulder","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"担ぐ","answer":["かつぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"printing type","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"活字","answer":["かつじ"]},
    {"meaning":"vitality, energy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"活力","answer":["かつりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"process","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過程","answer":["かてい"]},
    {"meaning":"course, curriculum","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"課程","answer":["かてい"]},
    {"meaning":"heating","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加熱","answer":["かねつ"]},
    {"meaning":"majority","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過半数","answer":["かはんすう"]},
    {"meaning":"to cover (with something)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"被せる","answer":["かぶせる"]},
    {"meaning":"god","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"神様","answer":["かみさま"]},
    {"meaning":"cargo, freight","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"貨物","answer":["かもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to wither, to die (plant), to be blasted (plant)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"枯れる","answer":["かれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to dry (clothes, etc.), to desiccate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乾かす","answer":["かわかす"]},
    {"meaning":"ventilation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"換気","answer":["かんき"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"関西","answer":["かんさい"]},
    {"meaning":"to feel, to sense","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感ずる","answer":["かんずる"]},
    {"meaning":"indirection, indirectness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"間接","answer":["かんせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"dry, arid, insipid, dehydrated","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乾燥","answer":["かんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"impressions, thoughts","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感想","answer":["かんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"observation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"観測","answer":["かんそく"]},
    {"meaning":"frigid zone","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"寒帯","answer":["かんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"government office, authorities","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"官庁","answer":["かんちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"packing (in cans), canning, canned goods, tin can","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"缶詰","answer":["かんづめ"]},
    {"meaning":"dry cell, battery","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乾電池","answer":["かんでんち"]},
    {"meaning":"eastern half of Japan, including Tokyo","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"関東","answer":["かんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) idea, notion, conception, (2) sense (e.g. of duty)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"観念","answer":["かんねん"]},
    {"meaning":"toast (drink)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乾杯","answer":["かんぱい"]},
    {"meaning":"Chinese Character-Japanese (e.g. dictionary)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"漢和","answer":["かんわ"]},
    {"meaning":"atmospheric pressure","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"気圧","answer":["きあつ"]},
    {"meaning":"changing clothes, change of clothes","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"着替え","answer":["きがえ"]},
    {"meaning":"locomotive, engine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"機関車","answer":["きかんしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"term, period","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"期限","answer":["きげん"]},
    {"meaning":"symbol, code","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"記号","answer":["きごう"]},
    {"meaning":"to mince, to carve, to engrave","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"刻む","answer":["きざむ"]},
    {"meaning":"standard, basis, criteria, norm","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"規準","answer":["きじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"rising, getting out of bed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"起床","answer":["きしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"guest seating","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"客席","answer":["きゃくせき"]},
    {"meaning":"parlor, guest room","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"客間","answer":["きゃくま"]},
    {"meaning":"lecture cancelled","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"休講","answer":["きゅうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"rest, relief, relaxation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"休息","answer":["きゅうそく"]},
    {"meaning":"allowance, grant, supply","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"給与","answer":["きゅうよ"]},
    {"meaning":"clear, pure, noble","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"清い","answer":["きよい"]},
    {"meaning":"strengthen, intensify, reinforce, solidify","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"強化","answer":["きょうか"]},
    {"meaning":"boundary","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"境界","answer":["きょうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) line, procession, (2) matrix (math)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"行列","answer":["ぎょうれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"fishing (industry)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"漁業","answer":["ぎょぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"curve","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"曲線","answer":["きょくせん"]},
    {"meaning":"order, rules, law","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"規律","answer":["きりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be careful, to pay attention, to take care","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"気を付ける","answer":["きをつける"]},
    {"meaning":"limits, boundary, domain, zone, sphere, territory","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"区域","answer":["くいき"]},
    {"meaning":"even number","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"偶数","answer":["ぐうすう"]},
    {"meaning":"daydream, fantasy, fancy, vision","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"空想","answer":["くうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"to punctuate, to cut off, to mark off, to stop, to put an end to","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"区切る","answer":["くぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"complaint, troubles, objection","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦情","answer":["くじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"pain, trouble","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦心","answer":["くしん"]},
    {"meaning":"ring finger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"薬指","answer":["くすりゆび"]},
    {"meaning":"lipstick","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"口紅","answer":["くちべに"]},
    {"meaning":"to distribute, to deliver","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"配る","answer":["くばる"]},
    {"meaning":"labourer, worker","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"工夫","answer":["くふう"]},
    {"meaning":"combination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"組合せ","answer":["くみあわせ"]},
    {"meaning":"to assemble, to set up, to construct","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"組み立てる","answer":["くみたてる"]},
    {"meaning":"honorific, term of respect","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"敬語","answer":["けいご"]},
    {"meaning":"form, formality, format, math expression","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"形式","answer":["けいしき"]},
    {"meaning":"knitting wool","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"毛糸","answer":["けいと"]},
    {"meaning":"longitude","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経度","answer":["けいど"]},
    {"meaning":"public entertainment, accomplishments, attainments","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"芸能","answer":["げいのう"]},
    {"meaning":"horse racing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"競馬","answer":["けいば"]},
    {"meaning":"defense, guard, policing, security","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"警備","answer":["けいび"]},
    {"meaning":"true adjective","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"形容詞","answer":["けいようし"]},
    {"meaning":"adjectival noun, quasi-adjective","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"形容動詞","answer":["けいようどうし"]},
    {"meaning":"surgical department","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"外科","answer":["げか"]},
    {"meaning":"fur, skin, pelt","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"毛皮","answer":["けがわ"]},
    {"meaning":"blood pressure","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"血圧","answer":["けつあつ"]},
    {"meaning":"blood","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"血液","answer":["けつえき"]},
    {"meaning":"monthly salary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"月給","answer":["げっきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"end of the month","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"月末","answer":["げつまつ"]},
    {"meaning":"indication, market trend, worry","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"気配","answer":["けはい"]},
    {"meaning":"smoky","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"煙い","answer":["けむい"]},
    {"meaning":"inaccessible place, sharp eyes","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"険しい","answer":["けわしい"]},
    {"meaning":"place of origin, habitat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原産","answer":["げんさん"]},
    {"meaning":"origin, primeval","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原始","answer":["げんし"]},
    {"meaning":"prefectural office","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"県庁","answer":["けんちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"limit, bounds","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"限度","answer":["げんど"]},
    {"meaning":"actually, really","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現に","answer":["げんに"]},
    {"meaning":"principle, theory, fundamental truth","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原理","answer":["げんり"]},
    {"meaning":"raw materials","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原料","answer":["げんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) dear, beloved, darling, (2) yearned for","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"恋しい","answer":["こいしい"]},
    {"meaning":"overbearing, coercive, pushy, forcible, high-handed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"強引","answer":["ごういん"]},
    {"meaning":"public nuisance, pollution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公害","answer":["こうがい"]},
    {"meaning":"public, community, public service, society, communal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公共","answer":["こうきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"industrial arts","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"工芸","answer":["こうげい"]},
    {"meaning":"cross","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交差","answer":["こうさ"]},
    {"meaning":"lecturer","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"講師","answer":["こうし"]},
    {"meaning":"formula, formality, official","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公式","answer":["こうしき"]},
    {"meaning":"excuse","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"口実","answer":["こうじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"perfume","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"香水","answer":["こうすい"]},
    {"meaning":"beam, light ray","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"光線","answer":["こうせん"]},
    {"meaning":"upper","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"高層","answer":["こうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"structure, construction","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"構造","answer":["こうぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"alternation, change, relief, relay, shift","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"交替","answer":["こうたい"]},
    {"meaning":"arable land","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"耕地","answer":["こうち"]},
    {"meaning":"transportation facilities","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交通機関","answer":["こうつうきかん"]},
    {"meaning":"campus","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"校庭","answer":["こうてい"]},
    {"meaning":"positive, affirmation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"肯定","answer":["こうてい"]},
    {"meaning":"high class, high grade","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"高等","answer":["こうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"combination, incorporation, union, amalgamation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合同","answer":["ごうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"official announcement, proclamation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公表","answer":["こうひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"mineral","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鉱物","answer":["こうぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"official business, public business","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公務","answer":["こうむ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) (Japanese) maple","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"紅葉","answer":["こうよう","もみじ"]},
    {"meaning":"rational","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合理","answer":["ごうり"]},
    {"meaning":"alternating current, intercourse, (cultural) exchange, intermingling","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交流","answer":["こうりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"confluence, union, linking up, merge","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合流","answer":["ごうりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"effect, efficacy, validity, potency","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"効力","answer":["こうりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"to exceed, to cross over, to cross","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"超える","answer":["こえる"]},
    {"meaning":"king","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"国王","answer":["こくおう"]},
    {"meaning":"nationality","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"国籍","answer":["こくせき"]},
    {"meaning":"to freeze, to be chilled, to be frozen","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"凍える","answer":["こごえる"]},
    {"meaning":"having some knowledge of, happening to know","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"心当たり","answer":["こころあたり"]},
    {"meaning":"to be informed, to have thorough knowledge","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"心得る","answer":["こころえる"]},
    {"meaning":"seat, bench","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"腰掛け","answer":["こしかけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to sit (down)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"腰掛ける","answer":["こしかける"]},
    {"meaning":"to cross, to pass, to tide over","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"超す","answer":["こす"]},
    {"meaning":"an individual","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"個体","answer":["こたい"]},
    {"meaning":"little finger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"小指","answer":["こゆび"]},
    {"meaning":"mixing, mixture","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混合","answer":["こんごう"]},
    {"meaning":"(enrolled) in school","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"在学","answer":["ざいがく"]},
    {"meaning":"again and again, repeatedly","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再三","answer":["さいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"national holiday, festival day","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"祭日","answer":["さいじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"marking, grading, looking over","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"採点","answer":["さいてん"]},
    {"meaning":"lumber, timber","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"材木","answer":["ざいもく"]},
    {"meaning":"reverse, inversion, upside down","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"逆さ","answer":["さかさ"]},
    {"question":"膝","answer":["ひざ"],"meaning":"knee, lap; knee and thigh (while sitting)"},
    {"meaning":"to search, to seek, to look for","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"捜す","answer":["さがす"]},
    {"meaning":"bar, bar-room","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"酒場","answer":["さかば"]},
    {"meaning":"some time ago","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"先程","answer":["さきほど"]},
    {"meaning":"frame, draw up, make, producing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"作成","answer":["さくせい"]},
    {"meaning":"to search, to look for, to sound out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"探る","answer":["さぐる"]},
    {"meaning":"to stick, to be stuck","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"刺さる","answer":["ささる"]},
    {"meaning":"hindrance, impediment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差し支え","answer":["さしつかえ"]},
    {"meaning":"deduction, subtraction, balance, ebb and flow, rise and fall","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差し引き","answer":["さしひき"]},
    {"meaning":"to pierce, to stab, to prick, to thrust","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"刺す","answer":["さす"]},
    {"meaning":"clever, adept, good, expectations, as one would expect","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流石","answer":["さすが"]},
    {"meaning":"noise (jarring, grating)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"雑音","answer":["ざつおん"]},
    {"meaning":"at once, immediately, without delay, promptly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"早速","answer":["さっそく"]},
    {"meaning":"cushion (Japanese)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"座布団","answer":["ざぶとん"]},
    {"meaning":"to cool, to dampen, to let cool","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"冷ます","answer":["さます"]},
    {"meaning":"to become cool, to wear off, to abate, to subside","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"冷める","answer":["さめる"]},
    {"meaning":"month after next","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再来月","answer":["さらいげつ"]},
    {"question":"衝突","answer":["しょうとつ"],"meaning":"collision; crash; running into, conflict; quarrel; clashing"},
    {"meaning":"year after next","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再来年","answer":["さらいねん"]},
    {"meaning":"triangle, triangular","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"三角","answer":["さんかく"]},
    {"meaning":"arithmetic","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"算数","answer":["さんすう"]},
    {"meaning":"producing area","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"産地","answer":["さんち"]},
    {"meaning":"mountain forest, mountains and forest","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"山林","answer":["さんりん"]},
    {"meaning":"temple","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"寺院","answer":["じいん"]},
    {"meaning":"salty (taste)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"塩辛い","answer":["しおからい"]},
    {"meaning":"square","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"四角","answer":["しかく"]},
    {"meaning":"square","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"四角い","answer":["しかくい"]},
    {"meaning":"timetable, schedule","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"時間割","answer":["じかんわり"]},
    {"meaning":"four seasons","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"四季","answer":["しき"]},
    {"meaning":"bringing, taking, carrying","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"持参","answer":["じさん"]},
    {"meaning":"rounding up (fractions)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"四捨五入","answer":["ししゃごにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to quieten down, to calm down, to subside","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"静まる","answer":["しずまる"]},
    {"meaning":"natural science","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"自然科学","answer":["しぜんかがく"]},
    {"meaning":"speed (per hour)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"時速","answer":["じそく"]},
    {"meaning":"descendants, posterity, offspring","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"子孫","answer":["しそん"]},
    {"meaning":"self-government, autonomy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"自治","answer":["じち"]},
    {"meaning":"feelings (actual, true)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実感","answer":["じっかん"]},
    {"meaning":"moisture, humidity, dampness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湿気","answer":["しっけ"]},
    {"meaning":"practice, training","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実習","answer":["じっしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"achievements, actual results","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"実績","answer":["じっせき"]},
    {"meaning":"level of humidity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湿度","answer":["しつど"]},
    {"meaning":"real thing, original","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実物","answer":["じつぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"practical use, utility","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実用","answer":["じつよう"]},
    {"meaning":"merit, efficiency, arms, force","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実力","answer":["じつりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"example, illustration","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実例","answer":["じつれい"]},
    {"meaning":"disappointed love, broken heart, unrequited love, be lovelorn","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"失恋","answer":["しつれん"]},
    {"meaning":"designation, specification, assignment, pointing at","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"指定","answer":["してい"]},
    {"meaning":"private railway","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"私鉄","answer":["してつ"]},
    {"meaning":"children, juvenile","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"児童","answer":["じどう"]},
    {"meaning":"to be wet, to become wet, to be damp","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湿る","answer":["しめる"]},
    {"meaning":"social science","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"社会科学","answer":["しゃかいかがく"]},
    {"meaning":"weak point, weakness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"弱点","answer":["じゃくてん"]},
    {"meaning":"garage, car shed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"車庫","answer":["しゃこ"]},
    {"meaning":"editorial, leading article","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"社説","answer":["しゃせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"(car) wheel","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"車輪","answer":["しゃりん"]},
    {"meaning":"dwelling, house, residence, address","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"住居","answer":["じゅうきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"gathering, assembly, meeting, set (math)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"集合","answer":["しゅうごう"]},
    {"meaning":"terminus, last stop (e.g train)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"終点","answer":["しゅうてん"]},
    {"meaning":"important point, lay stress on, colon, emphasis","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"重点","answer":["じゅうてん"]},
    {"meaning":"circumference, outskirts, environs, (computer) peripheral","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"周辺","answer":["しゅうへん"]},
    {"meaning":"director, high executive","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"重役","answer":["じゅうやく"]},
    {"meaning":"end, close, termination","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"終了","answer":["しゅうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) weight, (2) heavyweight boxer","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"重量","answer":["じゅうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"national holiday","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"祝日","answer":["しゅくじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"taking an examination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受験","answer":["じゅけん"]},
    {"meaning":"going to work, at work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出勤","answer":["しゅっきん"]},
    {"meaning":"predicate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"述語","answer":["じゅつご"]},
    {"meaning":"leading part, leading actor (actress)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"主役","answer":["しゅやく"]},
    {"meaning":"in order, in turn","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"順々","answer":["じゅんじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"pure heart, naivete, self-sacrificing devotion","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"純情","answer":["じゅんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"digestion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"消化","answer":["しょうか"]},
    {"meaning":"steam, vapour","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"蒸気","answer":["じょうき"]},
    {"meaning":"(measuring) ruler","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"定規","answer":["じょうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"commerce, trade, business","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商業","answer":["しょうぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"prize, monetary award","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"賞金","answer":["しょうきん"]},
    {"meaning":"trading company, firm","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商社","answer":["しょうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"taking a train, entraining","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"乗車","answer":["じょうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"fraction (part of), decimal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"小数","answer":["しょうすう"]},
    {"meaning":"shop, business firm","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商店","answer":["しょうてん"]},
    {"meaning":"disinfection, sterilization","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"消毒","answer":["しょうどく"]},
    {"meaning":"victory or defeat, issue (of battle)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勝敗","answer":["しょうはい"]},
    {"meaning":"evaporation, unexplained disappearance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"蒸発","answer":["じょうはつ"]},
    {"meaning":"prize, trophy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"賞品","answer":["しょうひん"]},
    {"meaning":"victory or defeat, match, contest, game, bout","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勝負","answer":["しょうぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"(col) urine, piss","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"小便","answer":["しょうべん","しょんべん"]},
    {"meaning":"fire station","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"消防署","answer":["しょうぼうしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"the front, honesty","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"正面","answer":["しょうめん"]},
    {"question":"芽","answer":["め"],"meaning":"sprout"},
    {"meaning":"table salt","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"食塩","answer":["しょくえん"]},
    {"meaning":"worker, mechanic, artisan, craftsman","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"職人","answer":["しょくにん"]},
    {"meaning":"book, publication","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"書籍","answer":["しょせき"]},
    {"meaning":"white or grey hair, trendy hair bleaching","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"白髪","answer":["しらが"]},
    {"meaning":"acquaintance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"知合い","answer":["しりあい"]},
    {"meaning":"materials, data","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"資料","answer":["しりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to believe, to believe in, to place trust in","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"信ずる","answer":["しんずる"]},
    {"meaning":"man-made, synthetic, artificial","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"人造","answer":["じんぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"bed, couch","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寝台","answer":["しんだい"]},
    {"meaning":"social sciences, humanities","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人文科学","answer":["じんぶんかがく"]},
    {"meaning":"(human) life","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人命","answer":["じんめい"]},
    {"meaning":"late at night","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"深夜","answer":["しんや"]},
    {"meaning":"forest, woods","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"森林","answer":["しんりん"]},
    {"meaning":"relation, kin","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"親類","answer":["しんるい"]},
    {"meaning":"course, direction, compass bearing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"針路","answer":["しんろ"]},
    {"meaning":"myth, legend","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"神話","answer":["しんわ"]},
    {"meaning":"marine products, fisheries","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"水産","answer":["すいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"water vapour, steam","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"水蒸気","answer":["すいじょうき"]},
    {"meaning":"drop of water","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"水滴","answer":["すいてき"]},
    {"meaning":"canteen, flask, water bottle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"水筒","answer":["すいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"water level, horizon","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"水平","answer":["すいへい"]},
    {"meaning":"horizon","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"水平線","answer":["すいへいせん"]},
    {"meaning":"youngest child","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"末っ子","answer":["すえっこ"]},
    {"meaning":"matter of taste","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"好き好き","answer":["すきずき"]},
    {"meaning":"figure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"図形","answer":["ずけい"]},
    {"meaning":"to cool oneself, to cool off, to enjoy evening cool","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"涼む","answer":["すずむ"]},
    {"meaning":"head, brains, intellect","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"頭脳","answer":["ずのう"]},
    {"meaning":"chart, diagram, graph","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"図表","answer":["ずひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"清む","answer":["すむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to print","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"刷る","answer":["する"]},
    {"meaning":"surname, family name","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"姓","answer":["せい"]},
    {"meaning":"customs house","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"税関","answer":["ぜいかん"]},
    {"meaning":"work (film, book)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"制作","answer":["せいさく"]},
    {"meaning":"nature, property, disposition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"性質","answer":["せいしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"clean copy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"清書","answer":["せいしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"cleaning","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"清掃","answer":["せいそう"]},
    {"meaning":"existence, being, survival","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"生存","answer":["せいぞん"]},
    {"meaning":"(member of) political party","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"政党","answer":["せいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"ability, efficiency","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"性能","answer":["せいのう"]},
    {"meaning":"distinction by sex, sex, gender","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"性別","answer":["せいべつ"]},
    {"meaning":"square","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"正方形","answer":["せいほうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"main gate, main entrance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"正門","answer":["せいもん"]},
    {"meaning":"coming into existence, arrangements, establishment, completion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"成立","answer":["せいりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be burdened with, to carry on back or shoulder","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"背負う","answer":["せおう"]},
    {"meaning":"with trouble, at great pains, long-awaited","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"折角","answer":["せっかく"]},
    {"meaning":"getting closer, drawing nearer, approaching","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"接近","answer":["せっきん"]},
    {"meaning":"to come in contact with, to connect, to attend, to receive","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"接する","answer":["せっする"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) connection, union, join, link, (2) changing trains","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"接続","answer":["せつぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"complete works","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全集","answer":["ぜんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"despotism, autocracy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"専制","answer":["せんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"ancestor","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"先祖","answer":["せんぞ"]},
    {"meaning":"head, lead, vanguard, first","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"先頭","answer":["せんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"(the) whole, universal, wholly, general","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"全般","answer":["ぜんぱん"]},
    {"meaning":"line, track, roadbed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"線路","answer":["せんろ"]},
    {"meaning":"difference, discrepancy, variation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相違","answer":["そうい"]},
    {"meaning":"increase and decrease, fluctuation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"増減","answer":["ぞうげん"]},
    {"meaning":"mutual, reciprocal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相互","answer":["そうご"]},
    {"meaning":"shipbuilding","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"造船","answer":["ぞうせん"]},
    {"meaning":"enlargement","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"増大","answer":["ぞうだい"]},
    {"meaning":"Prime Minister","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"総理大臣","answer":["そうりだいじん"]},
    {"meaning":"successively, one after another","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"続々","answer":["ぞくぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"express, special delivery","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"速達","answer":["そくたつ"]},
    {"meaning":"measurement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"測定","answer":["そくてい"]},
    {"meaning":"measurement, surveying","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"測量","answer":["そくりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"speed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"速力","answer":["そくりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"ancestor","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"祖先","answer":["そせん"]},
    {"meaning":"frankness, candour, openheartedness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"卒直","answer":["そっちょく"]},
    {"meaning":"(hum) to know","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"存じる","answer":["ぞんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"存ずる","answer":["ぞんずる"]},
    {"meaning":"loss and gain, advantage and disadvantage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"損得","answer":["そんとく"]},
    {"meaning":"to leave hospital","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"退院","answer":["たいいん"]},
    {"meaning":"contrast, antithesis, comparison","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"対照","answer":["たいしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"order, system, structure, set-up, organization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"体制","answer":["たいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"capacity, volume","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"体積","answer":["たいせき"]},
    {"meaning":"very much, exaggerated, very fine","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"大層","answer":["たいそう"]},
    {"meaning":"pronoun","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"代名詞","answer":["だいめいし"]},
    {"meaning":"rice planting","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"田植え","answer":["たうえ"]},
    {"meaning":"constantly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"絶えず","answer":["たえず"]},
    {"meaning":"to till, to plow, to cultivate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"耕す","answer":["たがやす"]},
    {"meaning":"bamboo, middle (of a three-tier ranking system)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"竹","answer":["たけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be saved, to be rescued, to survive, to be helpful","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"助かる","answer":["たすかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to fold (clothes)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"畳む","answer":["たたむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to compare, to liken, to speak figuratively, to illustrate, to use a simile","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"例える","answer":["たとえる"]},
    {"meaning":"reliable, trustworthy, hopeful, promising","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"頼もしい","answer":["たのもしい"]},
    {"meaning":"tabi, Japanese socks (with split toe)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"足袋","answer":["たび"]},
    {"meaning":"gradation, grade, stage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"段階","answer":["だんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"short term","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"短期","answer":["たんき"]},
    {"meaning":"coal mine, coal pit","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"炭鉱","answer":["たんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) defect, demerit, weak point, (2) disadvantage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"短所","answer":["たんしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"water outage","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"断水","answer":["だんすい"]},
    {"meaning":"singular (number)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"単数","answer":["たんすう"]},
    {"meaning":"multi-unit apartments","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"団地","answer":["だんち"]},
    {"meaning":"conclusion, decision","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"断定","answer":["だんてい"]},
    {"meaning":"short (e.g. story, film)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"短編","answer":["たんぺん"]},
    {"meaning":"to bring near, to put close, to let come near, to associate with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"近付ける","answer":["ちかづける"]},
    {"meaning":"to approach, to draw near","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"近寄る","answer":["ちかよる"]},
    {"meaning":"area, zone","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"地帯","answer":["ちたい"]},
    {"meaning":"site, point on a map","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"地点","answer":["ちてん"]},
    {"meaning":"neuter gender, neutral (chem.), indifference, sterility","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"中性","answer":["ちゅうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"in the middle, half-way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"中途","answer":["ちゅうと"]},
    {"meaning":"excess, being more than","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"超過","answer":["ちょうか"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) strong point, merit, (2) advantage","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"長所","answer":["ちょうしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"length, long and short, +-","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"長短","answer":["ちょうたん"]},
    {"meaning":"top, summit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"頂点","answer":["ちょうてん"]},
    {"meaning":"rectangle, oblong","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"長方形","answer":["ちょうほうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"condiment, seasoning","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"調味料","answer":["ちょうみりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"immediately following","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直後","answer":["ちょくご"]},
    {"meaning":"straight line","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"直線","answer":["ちょくせん"]},
    {"meaning":"just before","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直前","answer":["ちょくぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"direct communication","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直通","answer":["ちょくつう"]},
    {"meaning":"direct current","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直流","answer":["ちょくりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"storage, preservation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"貯蔵","answer":["ちょぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"right angle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"直角","answer":["ちょっかく"]},
    {"meaning":"to scatter around, to leave untidy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"散らかす","answer":["ちらかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to be in disorder, to lie scattered around","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"散らかる","answer":["ちらかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to scatter, to disperse, to distribute","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"散らす","answer":["ちらす"]},
    {"meaning":"to fall, to scatter (e.g. blossoms)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"散る","answer":["ちる"]},
    {"meaning":"addition, supplement, appendix","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"追加","answer":["ついか"]},
    {"meaning":"currency","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"通貨","answer":["つうか"]},
    {"meaning":"commuting to work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"通勤","answer":["つうきん"]},
    {"meaning":"passage, pathway","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"通路","answer":["つうろ"]},
    {"meaning":"to associate with, to keep company with, to get on with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"付合う","answer":["つきあう"]},
    {"meaning":"end (e.g. of street)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"突き当たり","answer":["つきあたり"]},
    {"meaning":"to run into, to collide with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"突き当たる","answer":["つきあたる"]},
    {"meaning":"to catch fire, (electricity) comes on","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"点く","answer":["つく"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to thrust, to strike, (2) to poke","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"突く","answer":["つく","つつく"]},
    {"meaning":"to rank next to, to come after","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"次ぐ","answer":["つぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"to make, to create","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"造る","answer":["つくる"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn on, to switch on, to light up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"点ける","answer":["つける"]},
    {"meaning":"to be handed down, to be introduced, to be transmitted","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"伝わる","answer":["つたわる"]},
    {"meaning":"to plunge into, to go into deeply","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"突っ込む","answer":["つっこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to serve, to fill a post, to serve under, to work (for)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"務める","answer":["つとめる"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to serve, to fill a post, to serve under, to work (for)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"努める","answer":["つとめる"]},
    {"meaning":"grain","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"粒","answer":["つぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be blocked, to be packed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"詰まる","answer":["つまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to pile up, to stack","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"積む","answer":["つむ"]},
    {"meaning":"an encounter","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出合い","answer":["であい"]},
    {"meaning":"restroom, lavatory, hand-washing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手洗い","answer":["てあらい"]},
    {"meaning":"fixed number of regular personnel, capacity (of boat, etc.)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"定員","answer":["ていいん"]},
    {"meaning":"fall, decline, lowering, deterioration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"低下","answer":["ていか"]},
    {"meaning":"commuter pass, season ticket","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"定期券","answer":["ていきけん"]},
    {"meaning":"regular holiday","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"定休日","answer":["ていきゅうび"]},
    {"meaning":"suspension, interruption, stoppage, ban","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"停止","answer":["ていし"]},
    {"meaning":"stopping (e.g. train)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"停車","answer":["ていしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"failure of electricity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"停電","answer":["ていでん"]},
    {"meaning":"to depart, to set out, to start, to be going out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出掛ける","answer":["でかける"]},
    {"meaning":"precise, accurate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"適確","answer":["てきかく"]},
    {"meaning":"wrist","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手首","answer":["てくび"]},
    {"meaning":"railway bridge, iron bridge","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鉄橋","answer":["てっきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"procedure, (legal) process, formalities","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手続き","answer":["てつづき"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting, reception","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出迎え","answer":["でむかえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to meet, to greet","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出迎える","answer":["でむかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to shine on, to illuminate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"照らす","answer":["てらす"]},
    {"meaning":"to shine","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"照る","answer":["てる"]},
    {"meaning":"biography, life story","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"伝記","answer":["でんき"]},
    {"meaning":"light bulb","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"電球","answer":["でんきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"marks, points, score, runs","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"点数","answer":["てんすう"]},
    {"meaning":"battery","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"電池","answer":["でんち"]},
    {"meaning":"here and there, little by little","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"点々","answer":["てんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"telephone pole, telegraph pole, lightpole","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"電柱","answer":["でんちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"electro-magnetic wave","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"電波","answer":["でんぱ"]},
    {"meaning":"electric current","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"電流","answer":["でんりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"enquiry, ENQ","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"問い合わせ","answer":["といあわせ"]},
    {"meaning":"copper","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"銅","answer":["どう","あかがね"]},
    {"meaning":"the same rank, equality, apposition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"同格","answer":["どうかく"]},
    {"meaning":"appointed day, very day","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当日","answer":["とうじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"letter to the editor, letter from a reader, contribution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"投書","answer":["とうしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"entry (on stage)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"登場","answer":["とうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"lighthouse","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灯台","answer":["とうだい"]},
    {"meaning":"theft, robbery","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"盗難","answer":["とうなん"]},
    {"meaning":"being on duty","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当番","answer":["とうばん"]},
    {"meaning":"lamp oil, kerosene","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灯油","answer":["とうゆ"]},
    {"meaning":"fairy tale","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"童話","answer":["どうわ"]},
    {"meaning":"to happen to pass by","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"通り掛かる","answer":["とおりかかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to melt, to dissolve","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"溶かす","answer":["とかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to dissolve (paint)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"溶く","answer":["とく"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to retreat, to recede, to withdraw","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"退く","answer":["どく","しりぞく","のく"]},
    {"meaning":"specific, special, particular","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"特定","answer":["とくてい"]},
    {"meaning":"to melt into","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"溶け込む","answer":["とけこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to melt, to thaw, to fuse, to dissolve","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"溶ける","answer":["とける"]},
    {"meaning":"to remove, to take away, to dislodge, to put something out of the way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"退ける","answer":["どける","しりぞける","のける"]},
    {"meaning":"alcove","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"床の間","answer":["とこのま"]},
    {"meaning":"barber","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"床屋","answer":["とこや"]},
    {"meaning":"here and there, some parts (of something)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"所々","answer":["ところどころ"]},
    {"meaning":"heart (of city)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"都心","answer":["としん"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to be fixed, (2) to abide, to stay (in the one place)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"留まる","answer":["とどまる","とまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to jump in, to leap in, to plunge into, to dive","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"飛び込む","answer":["とびこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to give shelter to, to lodge","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"泊める","answer":["とめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to seize, to grasp, to capture, to arrest","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"捕える","answer":["とらえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to harvest, to take in, to adopt","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り入れる","answer":["とりいれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to cancel","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り消す","answer":["とりけす"]},
    {"meaning":"to take out, to produce, to pick out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り出す","answer":["とりだす"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to adopt (measure, proposal), (2) to pick (fruit)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"採る","answer":["とる"]},
    {"meaning":"to take, to catch (fish), to capture","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"捕る","answer":["とる"]},
    {"meaning":"internist clinic, internal medicine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"内科","answer":["ないか"]},
    {"meaning":"phone extension, indoor wiring, inner line","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"内線","answer":["ないせん"]},
    {"meaning":"to cure, to heal, to fix, to correct, to repair","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"治す","answer":["なおす"]},
    {"meaning":"long, lengthy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"永い","answer":["ながい"]},
    {"meaning":"reconciliation, make peace with","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"仲直り","answer":["なかなおり"]},
    {"meaning":"to be prolonged, to drag on","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"長引く","answer":["ながびく"]},
    {"meaning":"middle finger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"中指","answer":["なかゆび"]},
    {"meaning":"intimate friend, bosom buddy, chum","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"仲良し","answer":["なかよし"]},
    {"meaning":"to lose someone, wife, child, etc","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"亡くす","answer":["なくす"]},
    {"meaning":"roadside tree, row of trees","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"並木","answer":["なみき"]},
    {"meaning":"to ring, to sound, to chime, to beat, to snort (nose)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"鳴らす","answer":["ならす"]},
    {"meaning":"south pole, Antarctic","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"南極","answer":["なんきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"South America","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"南米","answer":["なんべい"]},
    {"meaning":"to let loose, to set free, to let escape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"逃がす","answer":["にがす"]},
    {"meaning":"hateful, abominable, poor-looking, detestable","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"憎い","answer":["にくい"]},
    {"meaning":"to hate, to detest","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"憎む","answer":["にくむ"]},
    {"meaning":"odious, hateful","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"憎らしい","answer":["にくらしい"]},
    {"meaning":"daily lesson, daily work, daily routine","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"日課","answer":["にっか"]},
    {"meaning":"agenda","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日程","answer":["にってい"]},
    {"meaning":"dull (e.g. a knife), thickheaded, slow (opposite of fast), stupid","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鈍い","answer":["にぶい","のろい"]},
    {"meaning":"to heat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"熱する","answer":["ねっする"]},
    {"meaning":"sleep-wear, nightclothes, pyjamas, nightgown, nightdress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寝間着","answer":["ねまき"]},
    {"meaning":"sleep-wear, nightclothes, pyjamas, nightgown, nightdress","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"寝巻","answer":["ねまき"]},
    {"meaning":"agricultural produce","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農産物","answer":["のうさんぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"agricultural community, farm village, rural","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農村","answer":["のうそん"]},
    {"meaning":"concentration, brightness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"濃度","answer":["のうど"]},
    {"meaning":"agricultural chemicals","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農薬","answer":["のうやく"]},
    {"meaning":"all, entirely, completely, without exception","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"残らず","answer":["のこらず"]},
    {"meaning":"to lengthen, to stretch, to reach out, to grow (beard)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"延ばす","answer":["のばす"]},
    {"meaning":"to be prolonged","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"延びる","answer":["のびる"]},
    {"question":"芝生","answer":["しばふ"],"meaning":"lawn"},
    {"meaning":"grey, gray, ashen","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灰色","answer":["はいいろ"]},
    {"meaning":"to measure, to weigh, to survey","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"量る","answer":["はかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to measure, to weigh, to survey","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"測る","answer":["はかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to sweep, to brush, to gather up","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"掃く","answer":["はく"]},
    {"meaning":"gear, cog-wheel","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"歯車","answer":["はぐるま"]},
    {"meaning":"to get between, to be caught in","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"挟まる","answer":["はさまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to interpose, to hold between, to insert","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"挟む","answer":["はさむ"]},
    {"meaning":"underwear","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"肌着","answer":["はだぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"as was expected, really","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"果して","answer":["はたして"]},
    {"meaning":"expression (music), conceptualization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"発想","answer":["はっそう"]},
    {"meaning":"discussion, conference","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"話合い","answer":["はなしあい"]},
    {"meaning":"to accost a person, to talk (to someone)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"話し掛ける","answer":["はなしかける"]},
    {"meaning":"to leave, to get free, to cut oneself off","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"放れる","answer":["はなれる"]},
    {"meaning":"shuttlecock","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"羽根","answer":["はね"]},
    {"meaning":"fragment, splinter, broken piece","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"破片","answer":["はへん"]},
    {"meaning":"dentifrice, toothpaste","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"歯磨き","answer":["はみがき"]},
    {"meaning":"to flourish, to thrive, to be popular, to come into fashion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流行る","answer":["はやる"]},
    {"meaning":"to deposit, to pay in","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"払い込む","answer":["はらいこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to repay, to pay back","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"払い戻す","answer":["はらいもどす"]},
    {"meaning":"wire","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"針金","answer":["はりがね"]},
    {"meaning":"reflection, influence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"反映","answer":["はんえい"]},
    {"meaning":"seal (used for signature)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"判子","answer":["はんこ"]},
    {"meaning":"hurrah, cheers","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"万歳","answer":["ばんざい"]},
    {"meaning":"judge, judiciary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"判事","answer":["はんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"reflection, reconsideration, introspection, meditation, contemplation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"反省","answer":["はんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"house number, address","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"番地","answer":["ばんち"]},
    {"meaning":"peninsula","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"半島","answer":["はんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"exposure to the sun, sunny place","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日当たり","answer":["ひあたり"]},
    {"meaning":"to undertake, to take up, to take over","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引受る","answer":["ひきうける"]},
    {"meaning":"to repeat, to send back, to bring back","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引返す","answer":["ひきかえす"]},
    {"meaning":"subtraction","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"引算","answer":["ひきざん"]},
    {"question":"芝居","answer":["しばい"],"meaning":"play; drama"},
    {"meaning":"to detain, to check, to restrain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引き止める","answer":["ひきとめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be caught in, to be stuck in, to be cheated","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引っ掛かる","answer":["ひっかかる"]},
    {"meaning":"(taking) notes, copying","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"筆記","answer":["ひっき"]},
    {"meaning":"moving (dwelling etc.), changing residence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引越し","answer":["ひっこし"]},
    {"meaning":"to draw back, to sink, to cave in","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引っ込む","answer":["ひっこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"writer, author","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"筆者","answer":["ひっしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"index finger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人差指","answer":["ひとさしゆび"]},
    {"meaning":"cynicism, sarcasm","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"皮肉","answer":["ひにく"]},
    {"meaning":"skin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"皮膚","answer":["ひふ"]},
    {"meaning":"to cool, to refrigerate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"冷やす","answer":["ひやす"]},
    {"meaning":"beauty of figure or form","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"美容","answer":["びよう"]},
    {"meaning":"front cover, binding","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"表紙","answer":["ひょうし"]},
    {"meaning":"nap (at home), siesta","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"昼寝","answer":["ひるね"]},
    {"meaning":"bottling, bottled","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"瓶詰","answer":["びんづめ"]},
    {"meaning":"balloon","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"風船","answer":["ふうせん"]},
    {"meaning":"to deepen, to heighten, to intensify","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"深まる","answer":["ふかまる"]},
    {"meaning":"irregularity, unsteadiness, disorderly","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"不規則","answer":["ふきそく"]},
    {"meaning":"neighbourhood, vicinity, environs","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"付近","answer":["ふきん"]},
    {"meaning":"adverb","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"副詞","answer":["ふくし"]},
    {"meaning":"copy, duplicate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"複写","answer":["ふくしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"plural, multiple","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"複数","answer":["ふくすう"]},
    {"meaning":"to include, to instruct, to make one understand","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"含める","answer":["ふくめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to get late, to advance, to wear on","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"更ける","answer":["ふける"]},
    {"meaning":"sign, mark, symbol","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"符号","answer":["ふごう"]},
    {"meaning":"man and wife, married couple","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夫妻","answer":["ふさい"]},
    {"meaning":"radical (of a kanji character)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"部首","answer":["ぶしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"surface mail (ship)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"船便","answer":["ふなびん"]},
    {"meaning":"parts, accessories","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"部品","answer":["ぶひん"]},
    {"meaning":"snow storm","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"吹雪","answer":["ふぶき"]},
    {"meaning":"to increase, to add to, to augment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"増やす","answer":["ふやす"]},
    {"meaning":"literature, art and literature, belles-lettres","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"文芸","answer":["ぶんげい"]},
    {"meaning":"closure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"閉会","answer":["へいかい"]},
    {"meaning":"coolness, calmness, composure, unconcern","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平気","answer":["へいき"]},
    {"meaning":"(going) side by side, concurrent, abreast, at the same time","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"並行","answer":["へいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"weekday, ordinary days","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平日","answer":["へいじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"plain, open field","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平野","answer":["へいや"]},
    {"meaning":"editing, compilation, editorial (e.g. committee)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"編集","answer":["へんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"toilet, lavatory, rest room, latrine, comfort station","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"便所","answer":["べんじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"direction, way, compass point","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"方角","answer":["ほうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"prevention, check","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"防止","answer":["ぼうし"]},
    {"meaning":"objective, plan, policy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"方針","answer":["ほうしん"]},
    {"meaning":"packing, wrapping","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"包装","answer":["ほうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"law, rule","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"法則","answer":["ほうそく"]},
    {"meaning":"bandage, dressing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"包帯","answer":["ほうたい"]},
    {"meaning":"equation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"方程式","answer":["ほうていしき"]},
    {"meaning":"prevention of crime","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"防犯","answer":["ぼうはん"]},
    {"meaning":"direction, district, field (e.g., of study)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"方面","answer":["ほうめん"]},
    {"meaning":"to let go","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"放る","answer":["ほうる"]},
    {"meaning":"recruiting, taking applications","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"募集","answer":["ぼしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to air, to dry, to desiccate, to drain (off), to drink up","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"干す","answer":["ほす"]},
    {"meaning":"North Pole","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"北極","answer":["ほっきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"to dig, to excavate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"掘る","answer":["ほる"]},
    {"meaning":"headquarters","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"本部","answer":["ほんぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"the number of flat things","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"枚数","answer":["まいすう"]},
    {"meaning":"to wind, to coil, to roll","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"巻く","answer":["まく"]},
    {"meaning":"to bend, to crook, to lean","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"曲げる","answer":["まげる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be mixed, to be blended with, to associate with, to mingle with, to join","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混ざる","answer":["まざる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be mixed, to be blended with, to associate with, to mingle with, to join","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交ざる","answer":["まざる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be mixed, to be blended with, to associate with","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混じる","answer":["まじる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be mixed, to be blended with, to associate with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交じる","answer":["まじる"]},
    {"meaning":"to mix, to stir","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混ぜる","answer":["まぜる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be mixed, to be blended with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交ぜる","answer":["まぜる"]},
    {"meaning":"waiting room","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"待合室","answer":["まちあいしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to rendezvous, to meet at a prearranged place and time","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"待ち合わせる","answer":["まちあわせる"]},
    {"meaning":"total darkness, shortsightedness, pitch dark","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"真っ暗","answer":["まっくら"]},
    {"meaning":"to deify, to enshrine","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"祭る","answer":["まつる"]},
    {"meaning":"ticket window","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"窓口","answer":["まどぐち"]},
    {"meaning":"to mimic, to imitate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"真似る","answer":["まねる"]},
    {"meaning":"detour","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回り道","answer":["まわりみち"]},
    {"meaning":"full house, no vacancy, sold out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"満員","answer":["まんいん"]},
    {"meaning":"perfect score","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"満点","answer":["まんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"outward appearance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見掛け","answer":["みかけ"]},
    {"meaning":"itinerary, route","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"道順","answer":["みちじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be found, to be discovered","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見付かる","answer":["みつかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be familiar, to discover, to detect","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見付ける","answer":["みつける"]},
    {"meaning":"to look again, to get a better opinion of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見直す","answer":["みなおす"]},
    {"meaning":"to become used to seeing, to be familiar with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見慣れる","answer":["みなれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to bear fruit, to ripen","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実る","answer":["みのる"]},
    {"meaning":"to ask after (health), to visit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見舞う","answer":["みまう"]},
    {"meaning":"less than, insufficient","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"未満","answer":["みまん"]},
    {"meaning":"private, civilian, civil, popular, folk, unofficial","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"民間","answer":["みんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"to steam, to poultice, to be sultry","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"蒸す","answer":["むす"]},
    {"meaning":"group, crowd, flock, herd","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"群れ","answer":["むれ"]},
    {"meaning":"business card","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"名刺","answer":["めいし"]},
    {"meaning":"noun","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"名詞","answer":["めいし"]},
    {"meaning":"famous place","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"名所","answer":["めいしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"to command, to appoint","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"命ずる","answer":["めいずる"]},
    {"meaning":"superstition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"迷信","answer":["めいしん"]},
    {"meaning":"to aim at, to have an eye on","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"目指す","answer":["めざす"]},
    {"meaning":"(abbr) alarm-clock","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"目覚まし","answer":["めざまし"]},
    {"meaning":"mark, sign, landmark","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"目印","answer":["めじるし"]},
    {"meaning":"area","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"面積","answer":["めんせき"]},
    {"meaning":"interview","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"面接","answer":["めんせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"lumber, timber, wood","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"木材","answer":["もくざい"]},
    {"meaning":"table of contents","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"目次","answer":["もくじ"]},
    {"meaning":"storage room","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"物置","answer":["ものおき"]},
    {"meaning":"ruler, measure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"物差し","answer":["ものさし"]},
    {"meaning":"to burn","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"燃やす","answer":["もやす"]},
    {"meaning":"actor, actress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役者","answer":["やくしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"government office, public office","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役所","answer":["やくしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"government official","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役人","answer":["やくにん"]},
    {"meaning":"medicine(s), chemical(s)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"薬品","answer":["やくひん"]},
    {"meaning":"duty, business","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役目","answer":["やくめ"]},
    {"meaning":"pharmacy, drugstore","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"薬局","answer":["やっきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"破く","answer":["やぶく"]},
    {"meaning":"to get torn, to wear out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"破れる","answer":["やぶれる"]},
    {"meaning":"soft, tender, limp","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軟らかい","answer":["やわらかい"]},
    {"meaning":"amusement park","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遊園地","answer":["ゆうえんち"]},
    {"meaning":"evening paper","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"夕刊","answer":["ゆうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"friendship","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"友好","answer":["ゆうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"mailing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"郵送","answer":["ゆうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"bathrobe, informal summer kimono, yukata","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"浴衣","answer":["ゆかた"]},
    {"meaning":"steam, vapour","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湯気","answer":["ゆげ"]},
    {"meaning":"blood transfusion","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"輸血","answer":["ゆけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"transport, transportation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"輸送","answer":["ゆそう"]},
    {"meaning":"negligence, unpreparedness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"油断","answer":["ゆだん"]},
    {"meaning":"teacup","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湯飲み","answer":["ゆのみ"]},
    {"meaning":"lava","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"溶岩","answer":["ようがん"]},
    {"meaning":"infant, baby, child","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"幼児","answer":["ようじ"]},
    {"meaning":"capacity, volume","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"容積","answer":["ようせき"]},
    {"meaning":"use, usefulness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"用途","answer":["ようと"]},
    {"meaning":"point, gist, essentials, outline","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"要領","answer":["ようりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"too much, unnecessary, abundance, surplus, excess, superfluity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"余計","answer":["よけい"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to disgrace, to dishonour, (2) to pollute, to contaminate, to soil, to make dirty, to stain","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"汚す","answer":["よごす","けがす"]},
    {"meaning":"to collect, to gather, to add, to put aside","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寄せる","answer":["よせる"]},
    {"meaning":"four corners, crossroads","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"四つ角","answer":["よつかど"]},
    {"meaning":"preparation, preliminaries, reserve, spare","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予備","answer":["よび"]},
    {"meaning":"to call out to, to accost, to address (crowd), to appeal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"呼び掛ける","answer":["よびかける"]},
    {"meaning":"to summon, to call (e.g. phone)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"呼び出す","answer":["よびだす"]},
    {"meaning":"rude, violent, rough, lawless, unreasonable, reckless","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乱暴","answer":["らんぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"science","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"理科","answer":["りか"]},
    {"meaning":"advantages and disadvantages, interest","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"利害","answer":["りがい"]},
    {"meaning":"to abbreviate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"略す","answer":["りゃくす"]},
    {"meaning":"(river) basin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"流域","answer":["りゅういき"]},
    {"meaning":"both sides","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"両側","answer":["りょうがわ"]},
    {"meaning":"fisherman","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"漁師","answer":["りょうし"]},
    {"meaning":"consul","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"領事","answer":["りょうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"receipt, voucher","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"領収","answer":["りょうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"care-taking, caretaker, house-watching","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"留守番","answer":["るすばん"]},
    {"meaning":"exception","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"例外","answer":["れいがい"]},
    {"meaning":"zero, no marks","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"零点","answer":["れいてん"]},
    {"meaning":"freezing, cold storage, refrigeration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"冷凍","answer":["れいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"chain of islands","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"列島","answer":["れっとう"]},
    {"meaning":"union, alliance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連合","answer":["れんごう"]},
    {"meaning":"(audio) recording","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"録音","answer":["ろくおん"]},
    {"meaning":"to argue, to discuss, to debate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"論ずる","answer":["ろんずる"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese-English","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"和英","answer":["わえい"]},
    {"meaning":"youthful, young","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"若々しい","answer":["わかわかしい"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese clothes","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"和服","answer":["わふく"]},
    {"meaning":"division (math)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"割算","answer":["わりざん"]},
    {"meaning":"relatively, comparitively","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割と","answer":["わりと"]},
    {"meaning":"discount, reduction, rebate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割引","answer":["わりびき"]},
    {"question":"泡","answer":["あわ","あぶく"],"meaning":"bubble; foam; froth; head on beer"},
    {"meaning":"sweat, perspiration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"汗","answer":["あせ"]},
    {"meaning":"vicinity, nearby","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"辺り","answer":["あたり","ほとり"]},
    {"question":"騒がしい","answer":["さわがしい"],"meaning":"noisy; boisterous, turbulent (era, etc.); troubled"},
    {"question":"騒々しい","answer":["そうぞうしい"],"meaning":"noisy; boisterous"},
    {"meaning":"oil","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"油","answer":["あぶら"]},
    {"meaning":"stomach","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"胃","answer":["い"]},
    {"question":"養分","answer":["ようぶん"],"meaning":"nourishment; nutrient"},
    {"meaning":"force, vigor, energy, spirit","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"勢い","answer":["いきおい"]},
    {"question":"餅","answer":["もち"],"meaning":"sticky rice cake, mochi rice cake"},
    {"question":"飾り","answer":["かざり"],"meaning":"decoration"},
    {"meaning":"much more, still more, all the more","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"一層","answer":["いっそう"]},
    {"meaning":"general, liberal, universal, ordinary, average","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"一般","answer":["いっぱん"]},
    {"meaning":"removal, migration, movement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"移動","answer":["いどう"]},
    {"question":"飼う","answer":["かう"],"meaning":"to keep (a pet or other animal); to raise; to have; to own; to feed"},
    {"meaning":"(1) request, commission, dispatch, (2) dependence, trust","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"依頼","answer":["いらい"]},
    {"meaning":"medical care, medical treatment","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"医療","answer":["いりょう"]},
    {"question":"風邪","answer":["かぜ"],"meaning":"common cold; cold; influenza; flu; ague"},
    {"question":"題名","answer":["だいめい"],"meaning":"title"},
    {"question":"響く","answer":["ひびく"],"meaning":"to resound; to be heard far away, to reverberate; to shake; to vibrate, to come (home); to remain (with someone), to have an effect; to make an impression, to resound, to make a stir"},
    {"meaning":"printing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"印刷","answer":["いんさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"impression","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"印象","answer":["いんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"(hon) to visit, to ask, to inquire","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"伺う","answer":["うかがう"]},
    {"meaning":"to remove, to transfer, to infect","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"移す","answer":["うつす"]},
    {"meaning":"to betray, to turn traitor to, to double-cross","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"裏切る","answer":["うらぎる"]},
    {"question":"響き","answer":["ひびき"],"meaning":"commotion; stir, echo; reverberation, sound (esp. the distinctive sound of an object or activity, e.g. rain, gun, gallop, drum); noise, quality of a sound (e.g. a fine phrase, clear voice, resonant bell); feeling of a sound; emotion or feeling inspired by something heard or read"},
    {"meaning":"eternity, perpetuity, immortality","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"永久","answer":["えいきゅう"]},
    {"question":"靴下","answer":["くつした"],"meaning":"socks; sock; stockings; stocking"},
    {"meaning":"postponement, adjournment","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"延期","answer":["えんき"]},
    {"meaning":"acting, performance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"演技","answer":["えんぎ"]},
    {"question":"靴","answer":["くつ"],"meaning":"shoes; boots; footwear; footgear"},
    {"meaning":"to send, to give to, to award to, to confer on","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"贈る","answer":["おくる"]},
    {"meaning":"very young, childish","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"幼い","answer":["おさない"]},
    {"meaning":"band (e.g. conduction, valence)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"帯","answer":["おび"]},
    {"question":"青白い","answer":["あおじろい"],"meaning":"pale; pallid, bluish-white"},
    {"meaning":"counter for chapters (of a book)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"課","answer":["か"]},
    {"meaning":"pleasant, agreeable, comfortable","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"快適","answer":["かいてき"]},
    {"question":"雑巾","answer":["ぞうきん"],"meaning":"house-cloth; dust cloth"},
    {"question":"隣","answer":["となり"],"meaning":"neighbor (neighbour); next to (esp. living next door to)"},
    {"question":"隙間","answer":["すきま"],"meaning":"crevice; crack; gap; opening; clearance, spare moment; interval; break; pause; spare time, chink (in one's armor, armour); unpreparedness; carelessness"},
    {"meaning":"aroma, fragrance, scent, smell","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"香り","answer":["かおり"]},
    {"question":"長男","answer":["ちょうなん"],"meaning":"eldest son (may be the only son); first-born son"},
    {"question":"鑑賞","answer":["かんしょう"],"meaning":"appreciation (e.g. of art); aesthetic sense"},
    {"meaning":"pastry","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"菓子","answer":["かし"]},
    {"meaning":"wise, clever, smart","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"賢い","answer":["かしこい"]},
    {"meaning":"mold, model, style, shape, data-type","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"型","answer":["かた"]},
    {"question":"鐘","answer":["かね"],"meaning":"bell (often a large hanging bell); chime"},
    {"meaning":"to suffer","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"被る","answer":["かぶる"]},
    {"question":"鏡","answer":["かがみ"],"meaning":"mirror; looking-glass, barrel head"},
    {"question":"鉄砲","answer":["てっぽう"],"meaning":"gun, wooden pole that wrestlers strike in practice, fugu"},
    {"meaning":"leather","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"革","answer":["かわ"]},
    {"meaning":"can, tin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"缶","answer":["かん"]},
    {"meaning":"a patient","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"患者","answer":["かんじゃ"]},
    {"question":"鈴","answer":["すず","りん"],"meaning":"bell (often globular)"},
    {"question":"釣る","answer":["つる"],"meaning":"to fish; to angle; to catch, to lure in; to tempt; to attract; to entice; to allure"},
    {"question":"釣り合う","answer":["つりあう"],"meaning":"to balance; to be in harmony; to be in equilibrium, to suit; to go well together; to be a good match"},
    {"meaning":"machine, mechanism","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"機械","answer":["きかい"]},
    {"question":"釜","answer":["かま"],"meaning":"iron pot; kettle"},
    {"meaning":"bank, coast, shore","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"岸","answer":["きし"]},
    {"meaning":"engineer, technician","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"技師","answer":["ぎし"]},
    {"meaning":"pitiful, a pity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"気の毒","answer":["きのどく"]},
    {"question":"金魚","answer":["きんぎょ"],"meaning":"goldfish"},
    {"question":"重ねる","answer":["かさねる"],"meaning":"to pile up; to put something on top of another; to stack up, to repeat many times over; to go through something repeatedly"},
    {"meaning":"ex-","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"旧","answer":["きゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"game, match, contest","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"競技","answer":["きょうぎ"]},
    {"question":"酢","answer":["す"],"meaning":"vinegar"},
    {"meaning":"huge, gigantic, enormous","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"巨大","answer":["きょだい"]},
    {"meaning":"record, minutes, document","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"記録","answer":["きろく"]},
    {"question":"酔っ払い","answer":["よっぱらい"],"meaning":"drunkard"},
    {"meaning":"amount of money","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"金額","answer":["きんがく"]},
    {"meaning":"safe, vault, treasury, provider of funds","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"金庫","answer":["きんこ","かねぐら"]},
    {"question":"遭う","answer":["あう"],"meaning":"to meet; to encounter; to see, to have an accident; to have a bad experience"},
    {"question":"過剰","answer":["かじょう"],"meaning":"excess; surplus; over-"},
    {"meaning":"distinction, differentiation, classification","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"区別","answer":["くべつ"]},
    {"meaning":"native Japanese reading of a Chinese character","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"訓","answer":["くん"]},
    {"meaning":"army, force, troops","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軍","answer":["ぐん","いくさ"]},
    {"meaning":"practice, training","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"訓練","answer":["くんれん"]},
    {"meaning":"respect, honour","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"敬意","answer":["けいい"]},
    {"question":"通帳","answer":["つうちょう"],"meaning":"passbook; bankbook"},
    {"meaning":"tendency, trend, inclination","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"傾向","answer":["けいこう"]},
    {"question":"透き通る","answer":["すきとおる"],"meaning":"to be transparent; to be see-through, to be clear (voice)"},
    {"meaning":"(fine) art, the arts","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"芸術","answer":["げいじゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"drama, play","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"劇","answer":["げき"]},
    {"meaning":"theatre, playhouse","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"劇場","answer":["げきじょう"]},
    {"question":"逆様","answer":["さかさま"],"meaning":"inverted; upside down"},
    {"meaning":"prefecture","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"県","answer":["けん"]},
    {"question":"送料","answer":["そうりょう"],"meaning":"postage; carriage; shipping charge"},
    {"question":"送別","answer":["そうべつ"],"meaning":"farewell; send-off"},
    {"meaning":"construction, architecture","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"建築","answer":["けんちく"]},
    {"question":"迫る","answer":["せまる"],"meaning":"to approach; to draw near; to be imminent, to press (someone for something); to urge; to compel"},
    {"meaning":"thick (as of color, liquid), dense, strong","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"濃い","answer":["こい"]},
    {"question":"載る","answer":["のる"],"meaning":"to be placed on; to be set on; to be piled on; to be loaded on, to appear (in print); to be mentioned; to be recorded; to be reported; to be given"},
    {"meaning":"lecture, address","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"講演","answer":["こうえん"]},
    {"question":"載せる","answer":["のせる"],"meaning":"to place on (something), to give (someone) a ride; to give a lift; to pick up; to help on board, to load (luggage); to carry; to take on board, to send out (on the airwaves, etc.), to deceive; to take for a ride, to (sing) along with (musical accompaniment), to let (someone) take part, to excite (someone), to publish (an article); to run (an ad)"},
    {"meaning":"coin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"硬貨","answer":["こうか"]},
    {"question":"転がる","answer":["ころがる"],"meaning":"to roll; to tumble, to fall over; to roll over, to lie down, to be scattered about; to be common, (of a situation or outcome) to change; to turn out"},
    {"question":"転がす","answer":["ころがす"],"meaning":"to roll, to turn over; to tip over; to throw down, to leave, to buy and sell (quickly for a profit)"},
    {"meaning":"candidacy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"候補","answer":["こうほ"]},
    {"meaning":"ice, hail","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"氷","answer":["こおり"]},
    {"meaning":"to freeze, to be frozen over, to congeal","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"凍る","answer":["こおる"]},
    {"meaning":"quite, very","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"極","answer":["ごく"]},
    {"question":"車掌","answer":["しゃしょう"],"meaning":"(train) conductor"},
    {"question":"身分","answer":["みぶん"],"meaning":"social position; social status"},
    {"question":"蹴る","answer":["ける"],"meaning":"to kick, to refuse; to reject"},
    {"meaning":"national or state border","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"国境","answer":["こっきょう","くにざかい"]},
    {"meaning":"bone fracture","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"骨折","answer":["こっせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"parcel, package","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"小包","answer":["こづつみ"]},
    {"meaning":"flour, meal, powder","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"粉","answer":["こな"]},
    {"meaning":"wheat","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"小麦","answer":["こむぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"confusion, congestion","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混雑","answer":["こんざつ"]},
    {"meaning":"disorder, chaos, confusion, mayhem","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混乱","answer":["こんらん"]},
    {"meaning":"least, lowest, worst","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"最低","answer":["さいてい"]},
    {"question":"踏切","answer":["ふみきり"],"meaning":"railway crossing; railroad crossing; train crossing; level crossing, starting line; scratch, determination, stepping over the edge of the ring"},
    {"meaning":"border, boundary, mental state","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"境","answer":["さかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to go against, to oppose, to disobey, to defy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"逆らう","answer":["さからう"]},
    {"question":"跳ぶ","answer":["とぶ"],"meaning":"to fly; to soar, to jump; to leap; to spring; to bound; to hop"},
    {"meaning":"(1) token, label, (2) ticket, (3) charm","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"札","answer":["さつ"]},
    {"question":"跳ねる","answer":["はねる"],"meaning":"to jump; to leap; to prance; to spring up; to bound; to hop, to break up; to close; to come to an end, to hit (e.g. to have a car hit something or someone)"},
    {"meaning":"to sink, to feel depressed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"沈む","answer":["しずむ"]},
    {"meaning":"leadership, guidance, coaching","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"指導","answer":["しどう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to comprise, to account for, to make up (of), (2) to hold, to occupy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"占める","answer":["しめる"]},
    {"question":"足る","answer":["たる"],"meaning":"to be sufficient; to be enough; to be worthy of"},
    {"question":"赤道","answer":["せきどう"],"meaning":"equator"},
    {"question":"貼る","answer":["はる"],"meaning":"to stick; to paste; to affix, to stretch; to spread; to strain; to tighten; to put up (tent), to form (e.g. ice on a pond), to fill; to swell, to stick out; to put; to slap, to be expensive, to keep a watch on; to be on the lookout, to span; to generate"},
    {"meaning":"lodging","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"宿泊","answer":["しゅくはく"]},
    {"meaning":"publication","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"出版","answer":["しゅっぱん"]},
    {"meaning":"order, turn","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"順","answer":["じゅん"]},
    {"question":"貸間","answer":["かしま"],"meaning":"room to let; room for rent"},
    {"question":"貸家","answer":["かしや"],"meaning":"house for rent"},
    {"meaning":"(1) chapter, section, (2) medal","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"章","answer":["しょう"]},
    {"question":"謙遜","answer":["けんそん"],"meaning":"modesty; humility; being humble"},
    {"question":"調節","answer":["ちょうせつ"],"meaning":"regulation; adjustment; control"},
    {"meaning":"recognition, acknowledgement, approval, consent, agreement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"承認","answer":["しょうにん"]},
    {"question":"調整","answer":["ちょうせい"],"meaning":"adjustment; regulation; coordination; reconciliation; tuning; fixing; tailoring"},
    {"meaning":"plant, vegetation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"植物","answer":["しょくぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"signature","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"署名","answer":["しょめい"]},
    {"question":"話中","answer":["はなしちゅう"],"meaning":"busy (phone)"},
    {"question":"評論","answer":["ひょうろん"],"meaning":"criticism; critique"},
    {"meaning":"heart","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"心臓","answer":["しんぞう"]},
    {"question":"診断","answer":["しんだん"],"meaning":"diagnosis; medical examination"},
    {"question":"診る","answer":["みる"],"meaning":"to examine (medically)"},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"税","answer":["ぜい"]},
    {"meaning":"tax, duty","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"税金","answer":["ぜいきん"]},
    {"question":"訳す","answer":["やくす"],"meaning":"to translate; to interpret"},
    {"question":"見本","answer":["みほん"],"meaning":"sample; specimen; pattern, model; example"},
    {"meaning":"coal","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"石炭","answer":["せきたん"]},
    {"meaning":"oil, petroleum, kerosene","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"石油","answer":["せきゆ"]},
    {"question":"西暦","answer":["せいれき"],"meaning":"Christian Era; CE; anno domini; AD, Western (Gregorian) calendar"},
    {"meaning":"equipment, device, facilities, installation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"設備","answer":["せつび"]},
    {"meaning":"elephant","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"象","answer":["ぞう","しょう"]},
    {"meaning":"imagination, guess","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"想像","answer":["そうぞう"]},
    {"question":"裂く","answer":["さく"],"meaning":"to tear; to rip up, to cut up; to cleave; to cut open (esp. the abdomen), to forcibly separate (e.g. two lovers), to have a tattoo in the corner of one's eye"},
    {"meaning":"bottom, sole","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"底","answer":["そこ"]},
    {"meaning":"loss, disadvantage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"損","answer":["そん"]},
    {"meaning":"damage, injury, loss","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"損害","answer":["そんがい"]},
    {"meaning":"respect, esteem, reverence, honour","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"尊敬","answer":["そんけい"]},
    {"meaning":"respect, esteem, regard","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"尊重","answer":["そんちょう"]},
    {"question":"街角","answer":["まちかど"],"meaning":"street corner"},
    {"meaning":"target, object (of worship, study, etc), subject (of taxation, etc)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"対象","answer":["たいしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"cabinet minister","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"大臣","answer":["だいじん"]},
    {"meaning":"continent","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"大陸","answer":["たいりく"]},
    {"question":"行事","answer":["ぎょうじ"],"meaning":"event; function"},
    {"meaning":"valley","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"谷","answer":["たに"]},
    {"meaning":"ball, sphere, coin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"玉","answer":["たま","ぎょく"]},
    {"meaning":"simplicity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"単純","answer":["たんじゅん"]},
    {"question":"蚊","answer":["か"],"meaning":"mosquito"},
    {"meaning":"(in) charge","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"担当","answer":["たんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"area, region","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"地域","answer":["ちいき"]},
    {"meaning":"district, section, sector","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"地区","answer":["ちく"]},
    {"question":"虹","answer":["にじ"],"meaning":"rainbow"},
    {"question":"薬缶","answer":["やかん"],"meaning":"kettle"},
    {"meaning":"parking (e.g. car)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"駐車","answer":["ちゅうしゃ"]},
    {"question":"落第","answer":["らくだい"],"meaning":"failure; dropping out of a class"},
    {"question":"茶色い","answer":["ちゃいろい"],"meaning":"light brown; tawny"},
    {"question":"花火","answer":["はなび"],"meaning":"fireworks"},
    {"meaning":"author, writer","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"著者","answer":["ちょしゃ"]},
    {"question":"芯","answer":["しん"],"meaning":"wick; marrow; staple (for stapler); (pencil) lead; stuffing; pith, core; heart; centre; center"},
    {"meaning":"to pack, to shorten, to work out (details)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"詰める","answer":["つめる"]},
    {"question":"至急","answer":["しきゅう"],"meaning":"urgent; pressing"},
    {"question":"自衛","answer":["じえい"],"meaning":"self-defense; self-defence"},
    {"question":"脱線","answer":["だっせん"],"meaning":"derailment, digression; deviation"},
    {"meaning":"party (political)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"党","answer":["とう"]},
    {"meaning":"tower, pagoda","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"塔","answer":["とう"]},
    {"meaning":"verb","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"動詞","answer":["どうし"]},
    {"meaning":"poison, toxicant","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"毒","answer":["どく"]},
    {"question":"能率","answer":["のうりつ"],"meaning":"efficiency, moment (i.e. magnetic moment)"},
    {"meaning":"mud","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"泥","answer":["どろ"]},
    {"meaning":"relation, relationship","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"仲","answer":["なか"]},
    {"meaning":"company, fellow, colleague, associate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"仲間","answer":["なかま"]},
    {"question":"肘","answer":["ひじ"],"meaning":"elbow"},
    {"question":"羨む","answer":["うらやむ"],"meaning":"to envy"},
    {"question":"羨ましい","answer":["うらやましい"],"meaning":"envious (feeling, etc.); jealous, enviable (position, etc.)"},
    {"meaning":"cloth","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"布","answer":["ぬの"]},
    {"question":"縮小","answer":["しゅくしょう"],"meaning":"reduction; curtailment"},
    {"meaning":"tropics","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"熱帯","answer":["ねったい"]},
    {"meaning":"age, years","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"年齢","answer":["ねんれい"]},
    {"meaning":"farmer, farm family","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農家","answer":["のうか"]},
    {"meaning":"agriculture","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農業","answer":["のうぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"farmers, peasants","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農民","answer":["のうみん"]},
    {"question":"縮れる","answer":["ちぢれる"],"meaning":"to be wavy; to be curled; to be frizzled"},
    {"question":"縮める","answer":["ちぢめる"],"meaning":"to shorten; to reduce; to condense; to shrink, to crumple (fabric); to wrinkle, to make (one's body) smaller; to draw in (one's legs); to duck (one's head)"},
    {"meaning":"to state, to express, to mention","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"述べる","answer":["のべる"]},
    {"question":"縮む","answer":["ちぢむ"],"meaning":"to shrink; to contract; to diminish (in size)"},
    {"meaning":"ash","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灰","answer":["はい","あく"]},
    {"meaning":"explosion, detonation, eruption","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"爆発","answer":["ばくはつ"]},
    {"question":"緯度","answer":["いど"],"meaning":"latitude (nav.)"},
    {"question":"統一","answer":["とういつ"],"meaning":"unity; consolidation; uniformity; unification; compatible"},
    {"question":"索引","answer":["さくいん"],"meaning":"index; indices; indexes"},
    {"meaning":"to omit, to eliminate, to curtail, to economize","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"省く","answer":["はぶく"]},
    {"meaning":"needle, hand (e.g. clock)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"針","answer":["はり"]},
    {"question":"素質","answer":["そしつ"],"meaning":"character; qualities; genius; the makings of"},
    {"meaning":"light","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灯","answer":["ひ","ともしび"]},
    {"meaning":"damage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"被害","answer":["ひがい"]},
    {"question":"素直","answer":["すなお"],"meaning":"obedient; meek; docile; unaffected, honest; frank; upfront (about one's feelings)"},
    {"meaning":"second (60th min)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"秒","answer":["びょう"]},
    {"question":"純粋","answer":["じゅんすい"],"meaning":"pure; true; genuine; unmixed"},
    {"question":"納める","answer":["おさめる"],"meaning":"to dedicate; to make an offering; to pay (fees), to supply, to store, to finish; to bring to a close, to restore (something to its place), to achieve (e.g. a result)"},
    {"question":"系統","answer":["けいとう"],"meaning":"system, lineage; ancestry; family line, group (e.g. of colors) (colours); family (e.g. of languages); party; school (of thought), close (evolutionary) relationship, a population sharing a common ancestor (in genetics); strain (e.g. bacterial)"},
    {"meaning":"bag, sack","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"袋","answer":["ふくろ"]},
    {"meaning":"to defend (against), to protect, to prevent","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"防ぐ","answer":["ふせぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"twins, a twin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"双子","answer":["ふたご"]},
    {"question":"箸","answer":["はし"],"meaning":"chopsticks"},
    {"meaning":"usually, habitually, ordinarily, always","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"普段","answer":["ふだん"]},
    {"meaning":"writing brush","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"筆","answer":["ふで"]},
    {"meaning":"to shiver, to shake, to quake","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"震える","answer":["ふるえる"]},
    {"question":"等分","answer":["とうぶん"],"meaning":"division into equal parts"},
    {"meaning":"equilibrium, balance, average, mean","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"平均","answer":["へいきん","ならし"]},
    {"question":"空っぽ","answer":["からっぽ"],"meaning":"empty; vacant; hollow"},
    {"question":"稽古","answer":["けいこ"],"meaning":"practice; practising; training; study"},
    {"meaning":"pole, rod, stick","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"棒","answer":["ぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"gem, jewel","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"宝石","answer":["ほうせき"]},
    {"meaning":"abundance, wealth, plenty, bounty","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"豊富","answer":["ほうふ"]},
    {"question":"私立","answer":["しりつ"],"meaning":"private (establishment)"},
    {"meaning":"bone","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"骨","answer":["ほね","こつ"]},
    {"meaning":"grandchild","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"孫","answer":["まご"]},
    {"meaning":"festival, feast","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"祭","answer":["まつり"]},
    {"meaning":"circle, full (month), perfection, purity, suffix for ship names","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"丸","answer":["まる"]},
    {"meaning":"cavity, tooth decay, decayed tooth, caries","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"虫歯","answer":["むしば"]},
    {"question":"磨く","answer":["みがく"],"meaning":"to polish; to shine; to brush (e.g. teeth), to refine; to improve"},
    {"question":"確率","answer":["かくりつ"],"meaning":"probability; likelihood; chances"},
    {"meaning":"blanket","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"毛布","answer":["もうふ"]},
    {"meaning":"to burn","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"燃える","answer":["もえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to employ, to hire","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"雇う","answer":["やとう"]},
    {"question":"研修","answer":["けんしゅう"],"meaning":"training (esp. in-service); induction course"},
    {"meaning":"courage, bravery, valour, nerve, boldness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"勇気","answer":["ゆうき"]},
    {"meaning":"validity, availability, effectiveness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"有効","answer":["ゆうこう"]},
    {"question":"砂糖","answer":["さとう"],"meaning":"sugar"},
    {"meaning":"floor","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"床","answer":["ゆか","とこ"]},
    {"meaning":"abundant, wealthy, plentiful, rich","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"豊か","answer":["ゆたか"]},
    {"question":"知人","answer":["ちじん"],"meaning":"friend; acquaintance"},
    {"question":"瞳","answer":["ひとみ"],"meaning":"pupil (of eye), eye"},
    {"question":"真っ青","answer":["まっさお"],"meaning":"deep blue; bright blue, ghastly pale; pallid; white as a sheet"},
    {"meaning":"six (used in legal documents)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"陸","answer":["りく"]},
    {"question":"真っ先","answer":["まっさき"],"meaning":"the head; the foremost; beginning; the very front"},
    {"meaning":"change, money exchange","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"両替","answer":["りょうがえ"]},
    {"meaning":"ring, hoop, circle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"輪","answer":["わ","りん"]},
    {"meaning":"bay, gulf, inlet","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湾","answer":["わん"]},
    {"question":"一応","answer":["いちおう"],"meaning":"more or less; though not quite satisfactorily; after a fashion; pretty much; roughly; so far as it goes, tentatively; for the time being, just in case, once"},
    {"question":"一斉","answer":["いっせい"],"meaning":"simultaneous; all at once"},
    {"question":"看病","answer":["かんびょう"],"meaning":"nursing (a patient)"},
    {"question":"一通り","answer":["ひととおり"],"meaning":"(in) general; broad (e.g. knowledge); the basics, ordinary; usual; common, briefly; roughly, one method"},
    {"question":"看板","answer":["かんばん"],"meaning":"signboard; sign; billboard; hoarding; doorplate, draw; attraction; feature; highlight; spokesman; figurehead, reputation (of a shop), appearance; look, closing time"},
    {"question":"上下","answer":["じょうげ"],"meaning":"top and bottom; up and down; high and low; above and below; upper and lower ends, upside-down, top and bottom; high and low; above and below; upper and lower ends; up and down, going up and down; rising and falling; fluctuating, going and coming back, upper and lower classes; ruler and ruled; the government and the people, first and second volumes, samurai costume; old ceremonial costume, top and bottom; up and down; high and low; above and below; upper and lower ends, top and bottom; up and down; high and low; above and below; upper and lower ends, upper and lower classes; ruler and ruled; the government and the people"},
    {"question":"上旬","answer":["じょうじゅん"],"meaning":"first 10 days of month"},
    {"question":"下品","answer":["げひん","かひん"],"meaning":"vulgar; indecent; coarse; crude, inferior article​"},
    {"question":"下旬","answer":["げじゅん"],"meaning":"last third of a month; 21st to the last day of a month"},
    {"question":"下書き","answer":["したがき"],"meaning":"rough copy; draft; draught"},
    {"question":"下水","answer":["げすい"],"meaning":"drainage; ditch; gutter; sewerage, sewage; black water, water flowing underneath; one's true feelings, kanji \"water\" radical at bottom (radical 85)"},
    {"question":"下町","answer":["したまち"],"meaning":"low-lying part of a city (usu. containing shops, factories, etc.), Shitamachi (low-lying area of eastern Tokyo near Tokyo Bay, incl. Asakusa, Shitaya, Kanda, Fukugawa, Honjo, Nihonbashi, Kyobashi and surrounds)"},
    {"question":"下車","answer":["げしゃ"],"meaning":"alighting (from train, bus, etc.); getting off"},
    {"question":"直径","answer":["ちょっけい"],"meaning":"diameter"},
    {"question":"目覚し","answer":["めざまし"],"meaning":"alarm clock, opening one's eyes; keeping one's eyes open, type of candy given to a child after it wakes up from a nap"},
    {"question":"不通","answer":["ふつう"],"meaning":"suspension; interruption; stoppage; tie-up; cessation"},
    {"question":"不運","answer":["ふうん"],"meaning":"misfortune; bad luck; ill luck; ill fortune; bad break; tough luck; mischance"},
    {"question":"中世","answer":["ちゅうせい"],"meaning":"Middle Ages (in Japan esp. the Kamakura and Muromachi periods ); medieval times; mediaeval times"},
    {"question":"中味","answer":["なかみ"],"meaning":"contents; interior; substance; filling; (sword) blade"},
    {"question":"中旬","answer":["ちゅうじゅん"],"meaning":"middle of a month; second third of a month; 11th to 20th day of a month"},
    {"question":"中身","answer":["なかみ"],"meaning":"contents; interior; substance; filling; (sword) blade"},
    {"question":"主語","answer":["しゅご"],"meaning":"subject"},
    {"question":"丼","answer":["どんぶり"],"meaning":"porcelain bowl, bowl of rice with food on top"},
    {"question":"乾く","answer":["かわく"],"meaning":"to get dry"},
    {"question":"目立つ","answer":["めだつ"],"meaning":"to be conspicuous; to stand out"},
    {"question":"人通り","answer":["ひとどおり"],"meaning":"pedestrian traffic"},
    {"question":"代える","answer":["かえる"],"meaning":"to replace, to exchange; to interchange, to substitute"},
    {"question":"仮名遣い","answer":["かなづかい"],"meaning":"kana orthography; syllabary spelling"},
    {"question":"仮定","answer":["かてい"],"meaning":"assumption; supposition; hypothesis"},
    {"question":"目安","answer":["めやす"],"meaning":"criterion; standard; yardstick; reference; aim, rough estimate; approximation"},
    {"question":"会館","answer":["かいかん"],"meaning":"meeting hall; assembly hall"},
    {"question":"目下","answer":["めした"],"meaning":"subordinate; subordinates; inferior; inferiors; junior, at present; now"},
    {"question":"目上","answer":["めうえ"],"meaning":"superior; superiors; senior"},
    {"question":"体操","answer":["たいそう"],"meaning":"gymnastics; physical exercises; calisthenics"},
    {"question":"体系","answer":["たいけい"],"meaning":"system; organization; organisation; architecture"},
    {"question":"余所","answer":["よそ"],"meaning":"another place; somewhere else; strange parts, outside (one's family or group); those people, unrelated matter"},
    {"question":"侵入","answer":["しんにゅう"],"meaning":"invasion; incursion; raid; aggression; intrusion; trespass; penetration"},
    {"question":"便箋","answer":["びんせん"],"meaning":"writing paper; stationery"},
    {"question":"保健","answer":["ほけん"],"meaning":"health preservation; hygiene; sanitation"},
    {"question":"盛る","answer":["もる"],"meaning":"to prosper; to flourish, to copulate (animals), to serve (food, etc.); to dish out, to fill up; to pile up; to heap, to prescribe; to administer; to dose out, to put into (e.g. information in a report), to mark out (e.g. scale); to graduate (e.g. thermometer), to exaggerate; to apply heavy makeup"},
    {"question":"的確","answer":["てきかく"],"meaning":"precise; accurate; appropriate; exactly the right"},
    {"question":"発電","answer":["はつでん"],"meaning":"generation (e.g. power), sending a telegram; telegraphing"},
    {"question":"発射","answer":["はっしゃ"],"meaning":"firing; shooting; discharge; catapult, ejaculation"},
    {"question":"発売","answer":["はつばい"],"meaning":"sale; offering for sale; release (for sale); launch (product)"},
    {"question":"発つ","answer":["たつ"],"meaning":"to depart (on a plane, train, etc.)"},
    {"question":"申請","answer":["しんせい"],"meaning":"application; request; petition"},
    {"question":"傾らか","answer":["なだらか"],"meaning":"gently sloping; gentle; easy, smooth"},
    {"question":"儀式","answer":["ぎしき"],"meaning":"ceremony; rite; ritual; service"},
    {"question":"先端","answer":["せんたん"],"meaning":"pointed end; tip; fine point; spearhead; cusp; vanguard; advanced; leading edge; apex (of a curve)"},
    {"question":"免税","answer":["めんぜい"],"meaning":"tax exemption; duty exemption"},
    {"question":"全身","answer":["ぜんしん"],"meaning":"whole (body); full-length (e.g. portrait), systemic"},
    {"question":"公正","answer":["こうせい"],"meaning":"justice; fairness; impartiality"},
    {"question":"申し訳ない","answer":["もうしわけない"],"meaning":"I'm sorry; (it's) inexcusable; I feel regretful; I feel guilty, thank you very much (for help, etc.)"},
    {"question":"兵隊","answer":["へいたい"],"meaning":"soldier; sailor"},
    {"question":"兼ねる","answer":["かねる"],"meaning":"to be unable to; to find difficult (unpleasant, awkward, painful) to do, to serve two or more functions or roles simultaneously; to contain (or combine) two or more features, to work in two or more jobs simultaneously (positions, etc.); to do alongside, to hesitate to do something (out of consideration for others), to think of the future (as well as the present)"},
    {"question":"円い","answer":["まるい"],"meaning":"round; circular; spherical, harmonious; calm"},
    {"question":"写る","answer":["うつる"],"meaning":"to be photographed; to be projected"},
    {"question":"写生","answer":["しゃせい"],"meaning":"sketching; drawing from nature; portrayal; description"},
    {"question":"田んぼ","answer":["たんぼ"],"meaning":"paddy field; farm"},
    {"question":"生長","answer":["せいちょう"],"meaning":"growth; increment"},
    {"question":"生意気","answer":["なまいき"],"meaning":"impertinent; saucy; cheeky; conceit; audacious; brazen; feisty"},
    {"question":"出来上がり","answer":["できあがり"],"meaning":"finish; completion; ready; made for; cut out"},
    {"question":"分布","answer":["ぶんぷ"],"meaning":"distribution; allocation"},
    {"question":"分類","answer":["ぶんるい"],"meaning":"classification; categorization; sorting"},
    {"question":"初旬","answer":["しょじゅん"],"meaning":"first 10 days of the month"},
    {"question":"生年月日","answer":["せいねんがっぴ"],"meaning":"birth date; date of birth; DOB"},
    {"question":"刺身","answer":["さしみ"],"meaning":"sashimi (raw sliced fish, shellfish or crustaceans)"},
    {"question":"削る","answer":["けずる"],"meaning":"to shave (wood or leather); to sharpen; to plane; to whittle; to pare; to scrape off, to shave off (e.g. a budget, expenses, a salary, etc.); to curtail; to cut down, to cross out; to reduce; to curtail; to remove; to erase; to delete, to shave off (esp. concrete), to take a percentage; to take a cut"},
    {"question":"削除","answer":["さくじょ"],"meaning":"deletion; elimination; erasure; striking out"},
    {"question":"前後","answer":["ぜんご"],"meaning":"front and rear; front and back; before and behind; back and forth, before and after, order; context, consequences, inversion; reversion; getting out of order, co-occurring, around; about; approximately; nearly, front and rear; front and back; before and behind"},
    {"question":"剥く","answer":["むく"],"meaning":"to peel; to skin; to pare; to hull; to bare (e.g. fangs); to open wide (e.g. eyes)"},
    {"question":"生ずる","answer":["しょうずる"],"meaning":"to produce; to yield; to cause, to result from; to arise; to be generated"},
    {"question":"生け花","answer":["いけばな"],"meaning":"ikebana; Japanese art of flower arrangement, fresh flower; natural flower"},
    {"question":"力強い","answer":["ちからづよい"],"meaning":"powerful; strong; forceful; vigorous, reassuring; encouraging"},
    {"question":"功績","answer":["こうせき"],"meaning":"achievements; merit; meritorious service; meritorious deed"},
    {"question":"生える","answer":["はえる"],"meaning":"to grow; to spring up; to sprout, to cut (teeth)"},
    {"question":"動作","answer":["どうさ"],"meaning":"action; movements; motions; bearing; behaviour; behavior; execution; actuation; operation; manners"},
    {"question":"勘違い","answer":["かんちがい"],"meaning":"misunderstanding; wrong guess"},
    {"question":"匂う","answer":["におう"],"meaning":"to be fragrant; to smell (good), to stink; to smell (bad), to glow; to be bright, to smack of; to show hints of"},
    {"question":"包丁","answer":["ほうちょう"],"meaning":"kitchen knife; carving knife, cooking; food"},
    {"question":"区分","answer":["くぶん"],"meaning":"division; section; demarcation; partition; segmentation; subdivision; (traffic) lane; compartment; classification; sorting"},
    {"question":"半径","answer":["はんけい"],"meaning":"radius"},
    {"question":"南北","answer":["なんぼく"],"meaning":"north and south; north to south, South Korea and North Korea"},
    {"question":"瓶詰め","answer":["びんづめ"],"meaning":"bottling; bottled"},
    {"question":"原稿","answer":["げんこう"],"meaning":"manuscript; copy"},
    {"question":"瓦","answer":["かわら"],"meaning":"gram; gramme, roof tile"},
    {"question":"独り言","answer":["ひとりごと"],"meaning":"soliloquy; monologue; speaking to oneself"},
    {"question":"受話器","answer":["じゅわき"],"meaning":"(telephone) receiver"},
    {"question":"古典","answer":["こてん"],"meaning":"old book; classics; classic"},
    {"question":"句読点","answer":["くとうてん"],"meaning":"punctuation mark; punctuation marks"},
    {"question":"可決","answer":["かけつ"],"meaning":"approval; adoption (e.g. motion, bill); passage"},
    {"question":"司会","answer":["しかい"],"meaning":"leading a meeting; presiding over a meeting; officiating at a ceremony; chairmanship, chairman; presenter; host; moderator; master of ceremonies"},
    {"question":"名作","answer":["めいさく"],"meaning":"masterpiece"},
    {"question":"名字","answer":["みょうじ"],"meaning":"surname; family name"},
    {"question":"名物","answer":["めいぶつ"],"meaning":"famous product; special product; speciality; specialty"},
    {"question":"吐き気","answer":["はきけ"],"meaning":"nausea; sickness in the stomach"},
    {"question":"狙う","answer":["ねらう"],"meaning":"to aim at"},
    {"question":"問答","answer":["もんどう"],"meaning":"questions and answers; dialogue"},
    {"question":"嗅ぐ","answer":["かぐ"],"meaning":"to sniff; to smell"},
    {"question":"器具","answer":["きぐ"],"meaning":"utensil; apparatus; implement; device; gadget"},
    {"question":"狙い","answer":["ねらい"],"meaning":"aim"},
    {"question":"特長","answer":["とくちょう"],"meaning":"forte; merit"},
    {"question":"特色","answer":["とくしょく"],"meaning":"characteristic; feature; idiosyncrasy; personal colour, spot color (in printing)"},
    {"question":"特殊","answer":["とくしゅ"],"meaning":"special; particular; peculiar; unique"},
    {"question":"国立","answer":["こくりつ"],"meaning":"national"},
    {"question":"特売","answer":["とくばい"],"meaning":"special sale"},
    {"question":"地下水","answer":["ちかすい"],"meaning":"underground water"},
    {"question":"地味","answer":["じみ"],"meaning":"plain; simple; subdued; sober, soil fertility; product of the soil"},
    {"question":"地盤","answer":["じばん"],"meaning":"ground; crust (earth); bed (gravel, river, etc.), foundation (building, etc.); base, constituency; power base; support (electoral); footing; foothold"},
    {"question":"地質","answer":["ちしつ"],"meaning":"geological features, quality of a fabric or cloth; texture of a fabric"},
    {"question":"坊さん","answer":["ぼうさん"],"meaning":"Buddhist priest; monk, boy"},
    {"question":"坊っちゃん","answer":["ぼっちゃん"],"meaning":"son (of others), young master, green young man from a well-to-do family"},
    {"question":"物騒","answer":["ぶっそう"],"meaning":"dangerous; unsettled; troubled; disturbed; insecure"},
    {"question":"物語る","answer":["ものがたる"],"meaning":"to tell; to indicate"},
    {"question":"爪","answer":["つめ"],"meaning":"nail (e.g. fingernail, toenail); claw; talon; hoof, plectrum; pick, hook; clasp"},
    {"question":"基地","answer":["きち"],"meaning":"base (military, expedition, etc.)"},
    {"question":"基準","answer":["きじゅん"],"meaning":"standard; basis; criterion; norm; reference; datum"},
    {"question":"基盤","answer":["きばん"],"meaning":"foundation; basis; base; footing; infrastructure, bedrock, substrate (circuit board)"},
    {"question":"熟語","answer":["じゅくご"],"meaning":"kanji compound, idiom; idiomatic phrase"},
    {"question":"煮る","answer":["にる"],"meaning":"to boil; to simmer; to stew; to seethe"},
    {"question":"塞がる","answer":["ふさがる"],"meaning":"to be closed; to be blocked; to be healed (e.g. wound); to be shut up, to be clogged; to be plugged up, to be occupied; to be taken (e.g. accommodation)"},
    {"question":"塞ぐ","answer":["ふさぐ"],"meaning":"to stop up; to close up; to block (up); to plug up; to shut up; to cover (ears, eyes, etc.); to close (eyes, mouth), to stand in the way; to obstruct, to occupy; to fill up; to take up, to perform one's role; to do one's duty, to feel depressed; to mope"},
    {"question":"煮える","answer":["にえる"],"meaning":"to be boiled; to be cooked"},
    {"question":"売上","answer":["うりあげ"],"meaning":"amount sold; sales; proceeds; takings; turnover"},
    {"question":"売店","answer":["ばいてん"],"meaning":"shop; stand"},
    {"question":"売行き","answer":["うれゆき"],"meaning":"sales; demand"},
    {"question":"売買","answer":["ばいばい"],"meaning":"trade; buying and selling; trafficking (e.g. of humans, arms, drugs); dealing"},
    {"question":"夕日","answer":["ゆうひ"],"meaning":"evening sun; setting sun"},
    {"question":"夕立","answer":["ゆうだち"],"meaning":"(sudden) evening shower (rain)"},
    {"question":"夜行","answer":["やこう"],"meaning":"walking around at night; night train; night travel"},
    {"question":"大工","answer":["だいく"],"meaning":"carpenter"},
    {"question":"大木","answer":["たいぼく"],"meaning":"large tree"},
    {"question":"大通り","answer":["おおどおり"],"meaning":"main street"},
    {"question":"天皇","answer":["てんのう","すめらぎ"],"meaning":"Emperor of Japan"},
    {"question":"煎る","answer":["いる"],"meaning":"to parch; to fry; to fire; to broil; to roast; to boil down (in oil)"},
    {"question":"焦点","answer":["しょうてん"],"meaning":"focus (e.g. photographic); focal point"},
    {"question":"焦げる","answer":["こげる"],"meaning":"to burn; to scorch; to char; to singe"},
    {"question":"焦がす","answer":["こがす"],"meaning":"to burn; to scorch; to singe; to char"},
    {"question":"始終","answer":["しじゅう"],"meaning":"continuously; from beginning to end; from first to last"},
    {"question":"姿勢","answer":["しせい"],"meaning":"attitude; posture; stance; approach; carriage (of the body)"},
    {"question":"無限","answer":["むげん"],"meaning":"infinity; infinitude; eternity, infinite; limitless"},
    {"question":"娯楽","answer":["ごらく"],"meaning":"pleasure; amusement"},
    {"question":"嫌","answer":["いや"],"meaning":"disagreeable; detestable; unpleasant; reluctant"},
    {"question":"嫌がる","answer":["いやがる"],"meaning":"to hate; to dislike"},
    {"question":"孝行","answer":["こうこう"],"meaning":"filial piety"},
    {"question":"季節","answer":["きせつ"],"meaning":"season"},
    {"question":"定価","answer":["ていか"],"meaning":"list price; regular price; established price"},
    {"question":"宛名","answer":["あてな"],"meaning":"(addressee's) name; (recipient's) name and address"},
    {"question":"無数","answer":["むすう"],"meaning":"countless number; infinite number; innumerable"},
    {"question":"無地","answer":["むじ"],"meaning":"plain; unfigured"},
    {"question":"家屋","answer":["かおく"],"meaning":"house; building"},
    {"question":"容器","answer":["ようき"],"meaning":"container; vessel"},
    {"question":"寮","answer":["りょう"],"meaning":"hostel; dormitory, bureau (government department beneath a ministry under the ritsuryo system), office; official, chief; head"},
    {"question":"炊く","answer":["たく"],"meaning":"to cook (grains, e.g. rice), to boil; to simmer; to stew; to seethe"},
    {"question":"対策","answer":["たいさく"],"meaning":"measure; provision; step; countermeasure; counterplan; countermove"},
    {"question":"寿命","answer":["じゅみょう"],"meaning":"life span"},
    {"question":"封筒","answer":["ふうとう"],"meaning":"envelope"},
    {"question":"災難","answer":["さいなん"],"meaning":"calamity; misfortune; disaster"},
    {"question":"火山","answer":["かざん"],"meaning":"volcano"},
    {"question":"火口","answer":["かこう"],"meaning":"crater; caldera, burner (e.g. on a furnace), burner; nozzle; origin of a fire, tinder; touchwood; charcloth"},
    {"question":"屋外","answer":["おくがい"],"meaning":"outdoors; alfresco, outside near the door to one's home"},
    {"question":"展開","answer":["てんかい"],"meaning":"development; evolution; progressing; unfolding, expansion; spreading out; extending; deployment; building up, expansion"},
    {"question":"激増","answer":["げきぞう"],"meaning":"sudden increase"},
    {"question":"澄む","answer":["すむ"],"meaning":"to clear (e.g. weather); to become transparent"},
    {"question":"潰れる","answer":["つぶれる"],"meaning":"to be crushed; to be smashed; to be broken; to collapse, to become useless; to cease functioning; to be wasted (e.g. time), to go bankrupt; to go out of business; to fail"},
    {"question":"崩す","answer":["くずす"],"meaning":"to destroy; to demolish; to pull down; to tear down; to level, to disturb; to put into disorder; to throw off balance; to make shaky, to relax (one's pose); to make oneself at ease, to break (a bill); to change; to make change, to write in cursive style; to write in running style, to break into a smile; to let off a smile, to lower (a price)"},
    {"question":"崩れる","answer":["くずれる"],"meaning":"to collapse; to crumble, to get out of shape; to lose one's shape; to become disorganized; to become untidy, to break down; to be thrown into disarray, to crash (stock market); to slump; to decline, to break money into small change, to turn bad (e.g. weather); to change for the worse; to deteriorate"},
    {"question":"巡る","answer":["めぐる"],"meaning":"to go around, to return, to surround, to concern (usu. of disputes)"},
    {"question":"潰す","answer":["つぶす"],"meaning":"to smash; to crush, to shut down, to thwart; to block, to kill (time), to waste (e.g. talents)"},
    {"question":"工事","answer":["こうじ"],"meaning":"construction work; construction; work (related to construction, e.g. painting, concrete-pouring, etc.)"},
    {"question":"工員","answer":["こういん"],"meaning":"factory worker"},
    {"question":"帰す","answer":["かえす"],"meaning":"to send (someone) back; to send (someone) home, to come to (in the end); to end in, to attribute; to blame"},
    {"question":"滝","answer":["たき"],"meaning":"waterfall, rapids"},
    {"question":"渇く","answer":["かわく"],"meaning":"to be thirsty; to feel thirsty, to thirst for; to crave"},
    {"question":"消極的","answer":["しょうきょくてき"],"meaning":"negative; passive; half-hearted; unmotivated"},
    {"question":"広場","answer":["ひろば"],"meaning":"plaza; (public) square; piazza; forum; open space"},
    {"question":"店屋","answer":["みせや"],"meaning":"store; shop"},
    {"question":"海洋","answer":["かいよう"],"meaning":"ocean"},
    {"question":"建つ","answer":["たつ"],"meaning":"to be erected; to be built"},
    {"question":"強気","answer":["つよき"],"meaning":"confident; assured; self-assured; firm; strong; cocksure, bullish (e.g. market), great; grand, obstinate; stubborn"},
    {"question":"彫る","answer":["ほる"],"meaning":"to carve; to engrave; to sculpt; to chisel, to tattoo"},
    {"question":"派手","answer":["はで"],"meaning":"showy; loud; gay; flashy; gaudy"},
    {"question":"往復","answer":["おうふく"],"meaning":"making a round trip; going and returning; coming and going, round-trip ticket; return ticket, correspondence; exchanging (letters), socializing; visiting one another"},
    {"question":"後輩","answer":["こうはい"],"meaning":"junior (at work, school, etc.); younger people; younger student"},
    {"question":"御覧","answer":["ごらん"],"meaning":"(please) try to, (please) look, seeing; looking; watching"},
    {"question":"御辞儀","answer":["おじぎ"],"meaning":"bow; bowing"},
    {"question":"活躍","answer":["かつやく"],"meaning":"activity (esp. energetic); great efforts; conspicuous service, to flourish; to participate actively; to play an active role"},
    {"question":"心身","answer":["しんしん"],"meaning":"mind and body"},
    {"question":"洗剤","answer":["せんざい"],"meaning":"detergent; washing material"},
    {"question":"洋品店","answer":["ようひんてん"],"meaning":"shop that handles Western-style apparel and accessories"},
    {"question":"怪しい","answer":["あやしい"],"meaning":"suspicious; dubious; doubtful; dodgy; suspicious (referring to a potential amorous relation); dangerous (e.g. financial situation); ominous (e.g. weather); strange; shady; fishy, charming; bewitching; mysterious"},
    {"question":"恐縮","answer":["きょうしゅく"],"meaning":"feeling obliged; being grateful; being thankful; being sorry; being ashamed, shrinking back in fear"},
    {"question":"恨み","answer":["うらみ"],"meaning":"resentment; grudge; malice; bitterness, matter for regret; regret"},
    {"question":"恨む","answer":["うらむ"],"meaning":"to resent; to curse; to feel bitter; to blame; to bear a grudge, to regret"},
    {"question":"汁","answer":["しる","つゆ"],"meaning":"juice; sap, soup; broth, (dipping) sauce"},
    {"question":"水素","answer":["すいそ"],"meaning":"hydrogen (H)"},
    {"question":"悔しい","answer":["くやしい"],"meaning":"vexing; annoying; frustrating; regrettable; mortifying"},
    {"question":"悔やむ","answer":["くやむ"],"meaning":"to mourn; to lament, to be sorry; to regret; to repent"},
    {"question":"比較的","answer":["ひかくてき"],"meaning":"comparative; relative"},
    {"question":"惜しい","answer":["おしい"],"meaning":"regrettable; disappointing, precious; dear; valuable, too good for; deserving better, almost but not quite"},
    {"question":"意地悪","answer":["いじわる"],"meaning":"malicious; ill-tempered; unkind"},
    {"question":"意義","answer":["いぎ"],"meaning":"meaning; significance"},
    {"question":"感激","answer":["かんげき"],"meaning":"deep emotion; impression; inspiration"},
    {"question":"武士","answer":["ぶし"],"meaning":"warrior; samurai"},
    {"question":"憧れる","answer":["あこがれる"],"meaning":"to long for; to yearn after; to admire; to be attracted by"},
    {"question":"懐かしい","answer":["なつかしい"],"meaning":"dear; desired; missed"},
    {"question":"成分","answer":["せいぶん"],"meaning":"ingredient; component; composition"},
    {"question":"正味","answer":["しょうみ"],"meaning":"net weight, useful part; actual content, real; effective; full"},
    {"question":"標識","answer":["ひょうしき"],"meaning":"sign; mark; flag"},
    {"question":"桁","answer":["けた"],"meaning":"column; beam; girder; crossbeam; spar; yard, digit; decade; order of magnitude"},
    {"question":"校舎","answer":["こうしゃ"],"meaning":"school building"},
    {"question":"手拭い","answer":["てぬぐい"],"meaning":"(hand) towel"},
    {"question":"手頃","answer":["てごろ"],"meaning":"moderate; handy; convenient; reasonable"},
    {"question":"架空","answer":["かくう"],"meaning":"aerial; overhead, fictitious; imaginary; fanciful; fabricated"},
    {"question":"枕","answer":["まくら"],"meaning":"pillow; bolster, introduction (e.g. to a rakugo story); lead-in"},
    {"question":"東西","answer":["とうざい"],"meaning":"east and west, Orient and Occident; East and West, Ladies and Gentlemen!; Your attention, please!; roll-up, roll-up"},
    {"question":"東洋","answer":["とうよう"],"meaning":"Orient"},
    {"question":"拭く","answer":["ふく"],"meaning":"to wipe; to dry"},
    {"question":"挿す","answer":["さす"],"meaning":"to insert; to put in, to plant (a cutting); to strike, to arrange (flowers), to wear (a sword) in one's belt, to shut; to close; to lock; to fasten"},
    {"question":"捨てる","answer":["すてる"],"meaning":"to throw away; to cast away; to dump; to discard, to abandon; to desert; to leave, to give up; to resign"},
    {"question":"来日","answer":["らいにち"],"meaning":"arrival in Japan; coming to Japan; visit to Japan, future day; later date"},
    {"question":"推定","answer":["すいてい"],"meaning":"presumption; assumption, estimation"},
    {"question":"摩擦","answer":["まさつ"],"meaning":"friction; rubbing; rubdown; chafe"},
    {"question":"撮る","answer":["とる"],"meaning":"to take (a photo), to record (video, audio, etc.); to make (a film)"},
    {"question":"撮影","answer":["さつえい"],"meaning":"photography (still or motion); photographing; filming; shooting; (video) recording"},
    {"question":"攻める","answer":["せめる"],"meaning":"to attack; to assault; to assail"},
    {"question":"政治","answer":["せいじ"],"meaning":"politics; government"},
    {"question":"教わる","answer":["おそわる"],"meaning":"to be taught (by); to learn from"},
    {"question":"本棚","answer":["ほんだな"],"meaning":"bookshelves; bookshelf; bookcase"},
    {"question":"整う","answer":["ととのう"],"meaning":"to be ready; to be prepared; to be arranged, to be in order; to be put in order; to be well-ordered; to be well-proportioned; to be harmonious, to be adjusted; to be regulated; to be refined (e.g. of a face), to be settled (e.g. treaty, contract); to be completed"},
    {"question":"整備","answer":["せいび"],"meaning":"maintenance; servicing, putting in place; establishment; development; preparation; provision; outfitting"},
    {"question":"整数","answer":["せいすう"],"meaning":"integer"},
    {"question":"有無","answer":["うむ"],"meaning":"existence or nonexistence; presence or absence, consent or refusal; yes or no, flag indicator; presence or absence marker"},
    {"question":"有料","answer":["ゆうりょう"],"meaning":"toll; fee; charge; admission-paid"},
    {"question":"文体","answer":["ぶんたい"],"meaning":"literary style"},
    {"question":"文房具","answer":["ぶんぼうぐ"],"meaning":"stationery"},
    {"question":"月日","answer":["つきひ"],"meaning":"time; years; days, (the) date"},
    {"question":"書店","answer":["しょてん"],"meaning":"bookshop; bookstore"},
    {"question":"斜め","answer":["ななめ"],"meaning":"slanting; tilted; sloping; diagonal; oblique, unusual; slanted (view of the world); bad (mood)"},
    {"question":"斬る","answer":["きる"],"meaning":"to kill (a human) using a blade (sword, machete, knife, etc.); to slice (off); to lop (off); to cut (off)"},
    {"question":"方言","answer":["ほうげん"],"meaning":"dialect"},
    {"question":"日差し","answer":["ひざし"],"meaning":"sunlight; rays of the sun"},
    {"question":"日帰り","answer":["ひがえり"],"meaning":"day trip"},
    {"question":"日時","answer":["にちじ"],"meaning":"date and time"},
    {"question":"日用品","answer":["にちようひん"],"meaning":"daily necessities"},
    {"question":"日陰","answer":["ひかげ"],"meaning":"shade; shadow"},
    {"question":"早口","answer":["はやくち"],"meaning":"fast-talking; rapid talking"},
    {"question":"明け方","answer":["あけがた"],"meaning":"dawn"},
    {"question":"映す","answer":["うつす"],"meaning":"to project; to reflect; to cast (shadow)"},
    {"question":"映る","answer":["うつる"],"meaning":"to be reflected; to harmonize with (harmonise); to come out (photo); to be projected; to be displayed (on a screen)"}
  ]
}